
Bbl	O

RT	O
@	PER
Superhero_mikey	PER
:	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O
http://t.co/FPsdtnwrru	O

I	O
'm	O
sleepy	O
AF	O
.	O

http://t.co/IxjT9gUmbq	O
:	O
BININBOX	ORG
Women	O
's	O
Chiffon	O
Long	O
Sleeve	O
Casual	O
Blouse	O
Top	O
T-Shirts	O
BININBOX	ORG
Women	O
's	O
Chif	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/CIrNfaI4lk	O

#Streetstyle	O
#bbfo	O
London	LOC
Street	LOC
Life	O
http://t.co/mKyozhaVza	O

RT	O
@King_AlahDah	O
:	O
“	O
@_BREutiful	O
:	O
I	O
'm	O
a	O
Virgo	O
�?	O
�?	O

http://t.co/15JA4cEG8j	O

Man	O
Chappell	PER
bout	O
to	O
get	O
blocked	O
lol	O

RT	O
@	PER
carlyraejepsen	PER
:	O
Happy	O
Birthday	O
to	O
YOU	O
@	PER
justinbieber	PER
!	O
!	O
!	O
http://t.co/xRtwsVcTbB	O

People	O
loving	O
my	O
SnapChat	ORG
😂	O
😂	O

“	O
@	PER
SteveStfler	PER
:	O
Every	O
girl	O
says	O
this	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/9hy7TgBkfr	O
�?	O
@	PER
NoahEiden	PER

Dear	O
Twitter	ORG
,	O
sometimes	O
I	O
need	O
more	O
than	O
140	O
characters	O
to	O
describe	O
what	O
's	O
on	O
my	O
mind	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
"	O

GODDAMN	O

Y	O
'	O
all	O
do	O
n't	O
forget	O
that	O
Manu	PER
Ginobili	PER
is	O
the	O
Father	O
of	O
the	O
Flop	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
"	O
Flopping	O
"	O
to	O
the	O
Association	LOC
.	O

@	PER
delenasgasm	PER
haha	O
thank	O
you	O
x	O
yours	O
is	O
adorable	O
*	O
.	O
*	O

RT	O
@	PER
sharmansqueen	PER
:	O
how	O
am	O
i	O
supposed	O
to	O
get	O
over	O
allison	PER
argent	PER
's	O
death	O
it	O
doesnt	O
work	O
like	O
that	O

Grilled	O
Lamb	O
http://t.co/do7MZWETha	O

@	PER
CHIEF_PHREAKY	PER
yeah	O
I	O
been	O
fed	O
up	O
with	O
yo	O
ass	O
awhile	O
ago	O
.	O
Lol	O

“	O
@	PER
SnapchatProbbz	PER
:	O
If	O
I	O
send	O
you	O
an	O
ugly	O
snapchat	O
,	O
we	O
're	O
close	O
as	O
f	O
*	O
ck	O
.	O
�?	O
@	PER
JAIhhooo	PER

I	O
got	O
like	O
6	O
watches	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
them	O
broke	O
lol	O
FUCK	O
!	O

This	O
class	LOC
boring	O
.	O
.	O

Be	O
sure	O
to	O
follow	O
my	O
etsy	ORG
shop	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
adding	O
some	O
cute	O
wall	O
art	O
later	O
today	O
LauestShop	ORG
http://t.co/q0VHllG9al	O
via	O
@	ORG
Etsy	ORG
#etsy	O
#decoration	O

Loads	O
of	O
Game	LOC
Of	O
Thrones	O
stuff	O
going	O
on	O
in	O
my	O
TL	O
.	O
I	O
ai	O
n't	O
complaining	O
lol	O

🌸	O
Zayn	PER
Sunshine	PER
I	O
love	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
�?�	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
could	O
follow	O
me	O
because	O
it	O
means	O
that	O
you	O
actually	O
notice	O
that	O
I	O
exist	O
@	PER
zaynmalik	PER
🌸	O
dz	O

@aramonserrath	O
te	O
amoo	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/jdDUhS1kWf	O

Take	O
a	O
look	O
at	O
our	O
#blog	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
-	O
http://t.co/gTnLDDDzKr	O
@	ORG
lovecloth	ORG
#fashion	O
#fblogger	O
http://t.co/s0HiQjOzBe	O

RT	ORG
@FunnySayings	O
:	O
I	O
’	O
m	O
the	O
type	O
of	O
person	O
that	O
tries	O
to	O
fall	O
back	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
just	O
to	O
finish	O
a	O
dream	O
.	O

@	PER
DyrsRebater	PER
thank	O
youuu	O
dyrs	O
�?	O

@	PER
TimDrakeRobin3	PER
Smiles	O
.	O

Three	O
Things	O
I	O
Need	O
to	O
Stop	O
Doing	O
(	O
and	O
maybe	O
you	O
do	O
too	O
)	O
http://t.co/rarRnc5EuC	O
on	O
@	ORG
bloglovin	ORG

Logic	O
will	O
get	O
you	O
from	O
A	O
to	O
B	O
.	O
Imagination	O
will	O
take	O
you	O
anywhere	O
.	O
-	O
Albert	PER
Einstein	PER

@	PER
Breeeezzyyy	PER
22	O
days	O
till	O
I	O
'm	O
21	O
�?	O
�?	O

She	O
said	O
x	O
you	O
right	O
I	O
'm	O
your	O
only	O
friend	O

malapit	O
ko	O
na	O
makumpleto	O
libro	O
ni	O
Jodiiii	PER
:	O
"	O
)	O
3	O
nalang	O
yeheeeeyyy	O
tapos	O
hardbound	O
collection	O
na	O
~	O
woohoo	O

RT	O
@	PER
_youknowmalio	PER
:	O
@	PER
Jovonne_Mariah	PER
suuuure	O
it	O
is	O
haha	O
jk	O
I	O
know	O

http://t.co/DXTi9L08s7	O

When	O
Im	O
wearing	O
my	O
glasses	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Ima	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
Malik	PER

@	PER
YuJuNoinkyou	PER
BUT	O
I	O
DONT	O
THINK	O
THATS	O
GOING	O
TO	O
HELP	O
YOU	O
AT	O
ALL	O

21	O
things	O
every	O
Irish	O
person	O
in	O
Australia	LOC
should	O
know	O
http://t.co/06BR0KJyHB	O
via	O
@	PER
jenoconnell	PER

and	O
ca	O
n't	O
forget	O
the	O
fab	O
@AymsDesigns	O
@JoFreeRadio	O
@Bullring	O

If	O
liverpool	ORG
win	O
,	O
they	O
go	O
over	O
arsenal	ORG
on	O
goal	O
difference	O
#matchday	O
#lfc	ORG

awaken	O
the	O
soul	O

http://t.co/YAobRFp9Wc	O

"	O
@	PER
GoodMotivator	PER
:	O
The	O
first	O
wealth	O
is	O
health	O
.	O
"	O
#healthylifestyle	O
#wealthmanagement	O

Everybody	O
to	O
this	O
dixk	O

RT	O
@	PER
ArMalynAyien	PER
:	O
Lelaki	PER
yg	O
tak	O
reti	O
hargai	O
perempuan	O
ni	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
hell	LOC
😂	O
😂	O

@	PER
AshbyMaeee	PER
my	O
parents	O
were	O
like	O
"	O
omg	O
conn	O
u	O
can	O
not	O
drive	O
bc	O
u	O
r	O
a	O
rebel	O
and	O
skipped	O
traffic	O
skewl	O
"	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
like	O
http://t.co/I7BzcAl5IJ	O

RT	O
@	PER
reshma4	PER
:	O
On	O
set	O
with	O
my	O
boys	O
.	O
My	O
strange	O
boys	O
http://t.co/A4qVzM26er	O

I	O
miss	O
secondary	O
school	O
life	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
where	O
the	O
teachers	O
actually	O
gave	O
a	O
fuck	O
about	O
you	O
.	O

look	O
into	O
my	O
eyes	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
:3	O
http://t.co/KfjFjVlrVN	O

http://t.co/5zZF2oUo0L	O

@	ORG
Chipmonk_33	ORG
iyedeh	O
apekateloooooo	O
=	O
)	O
)	O

Really	O
?	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
New	O
cars	O
for	O
WEF	ORG
Africa	LOC
?	O
http://t.co/JwUMG8nsBJ	O
Click	O
here	O
to	O
read	O

That	O
moment	O
when	O
you	O
see	O
your	O
ex	O
with	O
someone	O
they	O
told	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
worry	O
about	O
.	O

good	O
smile	O
is	O
re-releasing	O
figmas	O
because	O
smash	O
bros	O
i	O
cant	O
believe	O

Avoiding	O
my	O
mom	O
forever	O
.	O

I	O
hate	O
school	LOC
and	O
I	O
hate	O
home	LOC
😪	O

Do	O
n't	O
follow	O
to	O
unfollow	O
cuz	O
I	O
have	O
&	O
been	O
having	O
the	O
app	O
,	O
so	O
if	O
u	O
unfollow	O
I	O
'll	O
unfollow	O
u	O
back	O
jst	O
like	O
that	O
.	O

RT	O
@	PER
NurseKimaaa	PER
:	O
Nursing	O
Sext	O
:	O
I	O
'm	O
gonna	O
use	O
my	O
tits	O
as	O
defibrillator	O
pads	O
.	O

No	O
tenen	O
(	O
?	O

I	O
have	O
you	O
now	O
!	O
#LardVader	PER
#AngryBirdsStarWars	ORG
http://t.co/8WgFCB7TR9	O

RT	O
@CapitalSTEEZ_	O
:	O
The	O
end	O
.	O

@Auqinar	O
it	O
's	O
the	O
best	O
😩	O

where	O
is	O
my	O
gay	O

RT	O
@	ORG
disneywords	ORG
:	O
Some	O
things	O
were	O
just	O
meant	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
's	O
you	O
and	O
me	O
.	O
–	O
Pooh	PER

@hoopfeed	O
would	O
be	O
interested	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
BU	ORG
hockey	O
or	O
football	O
coach	O
deals	O
with	O
their	O
players	O
.	O

The	O
MIND	O
PLAYING	O
COUNTRIES	O
TURKEY	LOC
CUP	O
.	O
PRESENTING	O
UEFA	ORG
and	O
FIFA	ORG
@	ORG
UEFAcom	ORG
@	ORG
FIFAcom	ORG

drink	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
#water	O

Only	O
just	O
noticed	O
this	O
it	O
's	O
a	O
nicotine	O
clear	O
patch	O
is	O
it	O
supposed	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
skin	O
like	O
that	O
anyone	O
know	O
x	O
http://t.co/3YnhWADAEG	O

@	PER
__BlANCS	PER
kiss	O
all	O
before	O
u	O
go	O
.	O
summertime	O
sadneeesss	O

RT	O
@VP__EZmoney_	O
_	O
:	O
S	O
/	O
O	O
To	O
The	O
Young	ORG
Dawgs	ORG
@	PER
mrminnoy22	PER
2	O
-	O
0	O
#EZMONEY	O
!	O
!	O

Nail	O
the	O
noteworthiness	O
regarding	O
financial	O
yet	O
amp-the	O
record	O
services	O
:	O
eaNzHM	O

Visit	O
http://t.co/jsMrpvuN9r	O
HAPPY	O
EGGSTRAVAGANZA	O
EASTER	O
GIVEAWAY	O
.	O
$	O
10	O
Amazon	ORG
Gift	O
Card	O
http://t.co/MIpIwKEMbx	O

RT	O
@Keys2the_Ash	O
:	O
I	O
hate	O
when	O
my	O
mom	O
try	O
to	O
talk	O
to	O
me	O
after	O
she	O
made	O
me	O
mad	O
.	O

110	O
flights	O
of	O
stairs	O
practice	O
✔	O
�?	O
9	O
-	O
11	O
Memorial	O
Stair	O
Climb	O
next	O
for	O
my	O
Dad	O
http://t.co/XbuOm7fP6N	O

@emzmac_xo	O
no	O
wonder	O
hahahahaha	O
they	O
were	O
steaming	O
and	O
your	O
shouting	O
abuse	O
at	O
a	O
poor	O
innocent	O
man	O
trying	O
to	O
get	O
home	O
from	O
work	O
hahahha	O

Time	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
sleep	O
before	O
they	O
see	O
these	O
tweets	O
and	O
file	O
a	O
report	O
and	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
graduate	O
.	O
Goodnight	O

RT	O
@	ORG
EnhamTrust	ORG
:	O
It	O
's	O
our	O
300th	O
tweet	O
.	O
Let	O
's	O
make	O
it	O
special	O
with	O
cake	O
!	O
Here	O
's	O
a	O
pic	O
of	O
Nick	PER
with	O
some	O
he	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
training	O
kitchen	O
http	O
:	O
…	O

RT	O
@	PER
Luke5SOS	PER
:	O
This	O
house	LOC
smells	O
like	O
tea	O
and	O
sounds	O
like	O
usher	PER

@	PER
KeatonStromberg	PER
follow	O
@	PER
stromsex	PER
&	O
@	PER
sunrisewithwes	PER
&	O
i	O
'll	O
kiss	O
u	O
!	O
they	O
're	O
block	O
,	O
they	O
cant	O
tweet	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
're	O
voting	O
#VoteChloeCrushSong	PER
5	O

double	O
glazing	O
windows	O
and	O
doors	O
for	O
Essex	LOC
http://t.co/eSDbVVAh3F	O

@	PER
DareTnzR	PER
I	O
thought	O
it	O
said	O
Vatican	LOC
.	O
.	O
.	O
Lol	O

@	PER
KymEllis	PER
Research	O
proposal	O
or	O
a	O
hangover	O
?	O
I	O
find	O
they	O
both	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
headache	O
.	O

RT	O
@	PER
tbhmclovin	PER
:	O
MIND	O
=	O
BLOWN	O
http://t.co/oxReImV3ni	O

http://t.co/2H9YbzPUft	O

http://t.co/r6PrFAsL9A	O

BUT	O
U	O
KNO	O
I	O
BEEN	O
JUGGIN	O
I	O
FUCKED	O
OVER	O
4	O
POUNDS	O
OF	O
MID	O
WHEN	O
WE	O
WAS	O
13	O

Austin	PER
its10	O
pm	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
go	O
to	O
sleep	O
happy	O
with	O
your	O
gnight	O
tweet	O
.	O
So	O
will	O
you	O
pls	O
tweet	O
me	O
?	O
Love	O
you	O
😿	O
😘	O
@	PER
AustinMahone	PER
6	O

Someone	O
call	O
,	O
Text	O
,	O
FT	O
,	O
oovoo	O
,	O
Skype	ORG
or	O
DM	ORG
me	O
it	O
's	O
that	O
serious	O
#Bored	O

@	PER
leejxngsk	PER
*	O
urwelcome	O

Hahahahaha	O
@	PER
Ejaaaeee	PER

fuck	O
i	O
forgot	O
my	O
eye	O
makeup	O
is	O
still	O
on	O
and	O
i	O
accidentally	O
rubbed	O
my	O
eye	O

RT	O
@	PER
5hStrategist	PER
:	O
I	O
want	O
the	O
girls	O
to	O
get	O
their	O
first	O
Moonman	PER
http://t.co/mvFs6F2Y5Q	O

She	O
's	O
Dating	O
The	O
Gangster	O
!	O
:	O
"	O
>	O
#BestMovieEver	O
#SDTG	O
#KathnielFan	PER
#Ican	O
tbreathe	O
http://t.co/Q1GDniXMGe	O

RT	O
@SmookCash	O
:	O
Half	O
of	O
these	O
niggas	O
just	O
want	O
a	O
name	O

Great	O
5	O
:	O
45	O
WOD	O
this	O
morning	O
at	O
@	ORG
CrossFitQueens	ORG
!	O
Finishing	O
#	O
1	O
in	O
my	O
class	O
made	O
it	O
that	O
much	O
sweeter	O
!	O
#crossfit	O
#chalk	O
http://t.co/f0qbEmTTEu	O

Only	O
God	O
know	O
the	O
best	O

I	O
guess	O
i	O
'll	O
just	O
order	O
my	O
kd	O
's	O
.	O
😒	O

@	PER
Grey_Steel_69	PER
@	PER
SoloFotoCasera	PER
@	PER
Boriricky	PER
@	PER
joel28610	PER
@	PER
cabi2716	PER
@	PER
BarSwinger2	PER
@	PER
parswnoredomx	PER
@	PER
SwingernewDF	PER

FREE	O
BEAT	O
!	O
!	O
FREE	O
BEAT	O
!	O
!	O
#NanoTherapy	O
http://t.co/ppwM3uNM6K	O
@Liso_The_Gawd	O
@	PER
priscilla560	PER

Wide	O
awake	O
.	O

pll	O
time	O
!	O
c	O
:	O

#JustCantGetEnough	O
#JustCantGetEnough	O
#JustCantGetEnough	O

Distance	O
in	O
relationship	O
can	O
cause	O
you	O
miss	O
someone	O
so	O
much	O
It	O
helps	O
to	O
realize	O
how	O
much	O
that	O
person	O
means	O
.	O
2	O

@	ORG
SM_TownNews	ORG
nooo	O
!	O

Just	O
posted	O
a	O
photo	O
http://t.co/5YKo1b4t1Z	O

@AmazingPhil	O
my	O
cat	O
scratches	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
hold	O
her	O
Phil	PER

I	O
posted	O
a	O
new	O
photo	O
to	O
Facebook	ORG
http://t.co/vxBO9uhras	O

My	O
eye	O
color	O
changes	O
between	O
blue	O
,	O
grey	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
really	O
weird	O
green	O
.	O
😳	O
#bye	O

The	LOC
Café	LOC
‘	O
Delicious	LOC
’	O
was	O
great	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
its	O
even	O
better	O
!	O
http://t.co/ZpbdVkGyTp	O
#Androidgames	O
#Android	ORG
#Gameinsight	O

Bout	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
campus	O
to	O
finish	O
this	O
project	O
then	O
work	O
until	O
7	O
😖	O
😩	O
😓	O
😞	O
idk	O
how	O
I	O
'm	O
bout	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
through	O
the	O
day	O

@	PER
SqueakyNisey	PER
though	O
lol	O

@	PER
Aliarazak	PER
eyhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh	O
dont	O
la	O
like	O
that	O
:(	O
(	O
(	O
(	O
(	O
(	O
(	O
i	O
cry	O
now	O

RT	O
@IntThings	O
:	O
When	O
thinking	O
about	O
life	O
remember	O
this	O
:	O
no	O
amount	O
of	O
guilt	O
can	O
solve	O
the	O
past	O
and	O
no	O
amount	O
of	O
anxiety	O
can	O
change	O
the	O
future	O

Limpopo	LOC
police	O
arrest	O
14	O
men	O
in	O
possession	O
of	O
explosives	O
http://t.co/JAMMn5J1Es	O
(	O
PIC	O
by	O
SAPS	O
)	O
http://t.co/5n1UjqJD1c	O

Types	O
of	O
Estate	LOC
Planning	O
a	O
Honolulu	LOC
,	O
HI	LOC
Lawyer	O
Can	O
Help	O
With	O
-	O
http://t.co/coMah2tup4	O

/	O
/	O
YELLS	O
/	O
/	O

@	PER
chejkayammouni	PER
natkasiema	O

P-R-A-C-T-I-C-E	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
how	O
I	O
spell	O
success	O
.	O

@BrainScratchSit	O
You	O
're	O
really	O
helping	O
.	O
He	O
's	O
still	O
annoying	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'm	O
much	O
more	O
relaxed	O
.	O
Thank	O
you	O
for	O
that	O
.	O

"	O
@	PER
tbhnoonecares	PER
:	O
always	O
that	O
one	O
person	O
in	O
your	O
squad	O
http://t.co/DAItgYv0xe	O
"	O
🙋	O
🙋	O
�?	O

I	O
procrastinate	O
for	O
uni	O
but	O
when	O
telling	O
#PrideOfBritain	ORG
why	O
#stephensstory	PER
needs	O
to	O
be	O
nominated	O
I	O
white	O
a	O
freaking	O
novel	O

Wind	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
mph	O
NW	O
.	O
Barometer	O
29	O
.	O
381	O
in	O
,	O
Falling	O
.	O
Temperature	O
57	O
.	O
0	O
°	O
F	O
.	O
Rain	O
today	O
0	O
.	O
08	O
in	O
.	O
Humidity	O
87	O
%	O

ITS	O
ONLY	O
WEDNESDAY	O
.	O
OMG	O
.	O
NOO	O
.	O

[	O
AUTOPLAY	O
WARNING	O
]	O
http://t.co/uk6AS2RkDY	O
New	O
URL	O
.	O

I	O
should	O
hurry	O
up	O
yaa	O
man	O

Man	ORG
Utd	ORG
not	O
naming	O
new	O
boss	O
this	O
week	O
http://t.co/sAUsQRji5v	O

RT	O
@	ORG
EXO_FANBASE	ORG
:	O
[	O
HQ	O
]	O
140414	O
Sehun	O
@	O
Gimpo	LOC
Airport	LOC
1	O
(	O
cr	O
:	O
the	O
prince	O
)	O
http://t.co/TpSVyoH4e3	O

@	PER
brionyjeaan_	PER
the	O
music	O
in	O
the	O
show	O
is	O
actually	O
flawless	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
perform	O
it	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
show	O
youll	O
die	O
its	O
so	O
perfect	O
so	O
many	O
songs	O
>	O

the	O
level	O
of	O
stress	O
technological	O
malfunctions	O
can	O
bring	O
into	O
your	O
life	O
is	O
unreal	O
.	O
#justaged10years	O

#FunFact	O
#Independent	O
is	O
self-supporting	O
:	O
not	O
forced	O
to	O
rely	O
on	O
another	O
for	O
money	O
or	O
support-to	O
function	O
/	O
operate	O
alone	O
#WeDV8	O
#1000Network	O

My	O
brother	O
wearing	O
a	O
purple	O
fake	O
eyelash	O
#family#funny	O
http://t.co/oi4nHyaj3Q	O

Mini	ORG
Countryman	O
or	O
Similar	O
Car	O
Rental	O
at	O
Corralejo	LOC
http://t.co/aF7w9szzBX	O

@gazmort97	O
are	O
you	O
and	O
me	O
mam	O
squidward	O
then	O
hahahaha	O

“	O
@	PER
MOWHETT	PER
:	O
Ghetto	O
Public	O
announcement	O
:	O
7	ORG
eleven	ORG
accepts	O
foodstamps	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Carry	O
on	O
�?	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O

When	O
there	O
's	O
drama	O
on	O
twitter	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
at	O
school	O
everyone	O
is	O
asking	O
you	O
about	O
it	O
#Vote1DUK	O
#KCA	O
http://t.co/WYM9zIImbd	O

@	PER
null	PER
0	O
.	O
2291686506322067	O

Terio	PER
's	O
weight	O
is	O
a	O
real	O
problem	O
�?	O

RT	ORG
@	PER
Tomaatojuice	PER
:	O
Gimme	O
a	O
cigarette	O
and	O
a	O
lighter	O
please	O
🔥	O
.	O

💀	O
“	O
@	PER
OhSo_Pretty	PER
:	O
I	O
be	O
feeling	O
like	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
drive	O
thru	O
🎤	O
http://t.co/dBIXSfgDml	O
�?	O

“	O
@	PER
LyssaDoe_	PER
:	O
Most	O
y	O
'	O
all	O
dudes	O
ai	O
n't	O
doin	O
shit	O
but	O
makin	O
mixtapes	O
&	O
babies	O
.	O
�?	O
Lol	O

@BBYUNOT	O
followed	O

Ya	O
i	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
hurting	O
me	O
,	O
only	O
made	O
things	O
darker	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

RT	O
@	ORG
HiSpiritsUK	ORG
:	O
Our	O
new	O
product	O
@TitosVodka	O
is	O
naturally	O
#gultenfree	O
available	O
@	ORG
SpiritCellarUK	ORG
http://t.co/bn9ZcLwdfG	O
http://t.co/4Rg4YJ0…	O

Luke	PER
Bryan	PER
is	O
older	O
than	O
my	O
dad	O
😳	O

RT	O
@	PER
TheFunnyVines	PER
:	O
Mom	O
:	O
Why	O
are	O
n't	O
you	O
in	O
a	O
relationship	O
yet	O
?	O
Me	O
:	O
https://t.co/GbEy8sjTN4	O

@	PER
RishaMae_07	PER
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O

RT	O
@dzrkkkk	O
:	O
RFT	ORG
!	O
"	O
@	PER
Karennn12_	PER
:	O
Hate	O
when	O
I	O
feel	O
like	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
one	O
to	O
talk	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
it	O
comes	O
down	O
to	O
it	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
even	O
say	O
what	O
's	O
wrong	O
.	O
"	O

@	O
Official	O
IsidingoThis	ORG
Bradley	PER
Haines	PER
guy	O
is	O
really	O
convincing	O
on	O
the	O
roal	O
he	O
play	O
,	O
confused	O
&	O
scared	O
in	O
cells	O
,	O
his	O
gud	O

The	O
SocioMan	O
Daily	O
is	O
out	O
!	O
http://t.co/hQHmtHTd58	O

I	O
do	O
n't	O
have	O
time	O
for	O
games	O
when	O
there	O
's	O
another	O
life	O
involved	O
!	O
Fuck	O
the	O
bullshit	O
!	O

RT	O
@	PER
patrickgjackson	PER
:	O
Will	O
the	O
Ukrainian	LOC
army	O
take	O
orders	O
from	O
the	O
revolutionary	O
government	O
in	O
Kiev	LOC
?	O
What	O
does	O
Putin	PER
regard	O
as	O
"	O
normalisatio	O
…	O

@	PER
PrettyMe_Esha	PER
@	ORG
_97Dollas	ORG
ima	O
need	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
sleep	O
NOW	O
✌	O
�?	O
👋	O
👋	O
👋	O

@	PER
2PMagreement211	PER
kekeke	O

(	O
RAW	O
)	O
RJOM	O
120400	O
Z	O
22007	O
KT	O
9999	O
FEW	O
006	O
SCT	O
070	O
23	O
/	O
20	O
Q	O
0997	O

When	O
we	O
discover	O
our	O
authentic	O
purpose	O
,	O
out	O
life	O
takes	O
on	O
a	O
whole	O
new	O
meaning	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
better	O
.	O

RT	O
@	ORG
ThatOneGoodVibe	ORG
:	O
My	O
kind	O
of	O
night	O
:	O
Outside	O
Hammock	O
Blunts	O
Bonfire	O
Friends	O
Laughter	O
Amazing	O
music	O
Nice	O
breeze	O
✨	O

@	PER
Lou_Manati	PER
from	O
who	O
?	O
!	O
Lol	O
that	O
's	O
so	O
random	O

RT	O
@Cool_Tweetsss	O
:	O
I	O
've	O
seen	O
enough	O
http://t.co/J4C0sbFsek	O

@	PER
justinbieber	PER
Happy	O
birthday	O
,	O
thanks	O
for	O
everything	O
,	O
you	O
're	O
my	O
idol	O
,	O
my	O
world	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
're	O
happy	O
I	O
'm	O
happy	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
smile	O
i	O
smile	O
i	O
love	O
you	O

I	O
really	O
dont	O
feeel	O
good	O

RT	O
@	PER
rdzaminhat	PER
:	O
When	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
on	O
most	O
days	O
all	O
he	O
thought	O
about	O
was	O
having	O
a	O
life	O
together	O
in	O
Bangi	LOC
.	O
Bangi	LOC
was	O
random	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
…	O

Follow	O
me	O
on	O
Instagram-	O
>	O
http://t.co/KbCCTTMuQp	O
or	O
just	O
search	O
@	PER
djryuma	PER

My	O
snapchat	ORG
makes	O
no	O
sense	O
since	O
im	O
no	O
longer	O
a	O
red	O
head	O
lol	O

@	PER
jenifermeer	PER
@	PER
jamesmolock	PER
@	PER
marciasavarese	PER
@	PER
amymartin3334	PER
well	O
happy	O
for	O
you	O
&	O
💙	O
so	O
enjoying	O
desert	O
!	O

We	O
're	O
busy	O
prepping	O
our	O
stage	O
for	O
SHIRLEY	PER
VALENTINE	PER
which	O
begins	O
performances	O
next	O
week	O
!	O
From	O
the	O
land	O
of	O
The	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/WKET4tPBHb	O

@	PER
HumanityTraitor	PER
(	O
Hooray	O
~	O
/	O
?	O
Let	O
's	O
celebrate	O
it	O
/	O
motong	O
nasi	O
tumpeng	O
/	O
?	O
)	O

Aula	O
(	O
?	O
)	O
http://t.co/4i4lXX7nCT	O

iPhone	O
#SelenaForMMVA	PER

The	O
only	O
solution	O
of	O
this	O
is	O
nothing	O
but	O
revolution	O
which	O
will	O
prevail	O
soon	O
.	O
#ModelTownTragedy	O

L	O
4	O
D	O
2	O
today	O
with	O
@	PER
theresadrianne	PER
@	PER
Ahjumalihuaaa	PER
@Za108	O
Raj	O
&	O
Gab	O
was	O
so	O
worth	O
it	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

like	O
a	O
drum	O
baby	O
do	O
n't	O
stop	O
beating	O

You	O
could	O
miss	O
your	O
chance	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
take	O
immediate	O
action	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
More	O
for	O
Taurus	O
http://t.co/QTphsZKgNr	O

RT	O
@	PER
Daveviena	PER
:	O
@	PER
DiashaBabii	PER
lmfaoooo	O
finally	O

I	O
'	O
M	O
SOO	O
FREAKINGG	O
HAPPY	O
FOR	O
NIALL	PER
!	O
HE	O
'S	O
BACKK	O
!	O
:*	O

RT	O
@	PER
iconapop	PER
:	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
sleeeeep	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
think	O
its	O
a	O
mix	O
between	O
jetlag	O
and	O
excitement	O
for	O
the	O
#theprismaticworldtour	O
with	O
@	PER
katyperry	PER
tomorrow	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
…	O

@THEPROFESSOR_JT	O
@	PER
maxjoseph	PER
annnnnndddd	O
shit	O
!	O

More	O
@	ORG
CBCNews	ORG
on	O
#Microsoft	ORG
announcing	O
18	O
,	O
000	O
job	O
cuts	O
around	O
the	O
world	O
over	O
the	O
next	O
year	O
in	O
wake	O
of	O
Nokia	ORG
purchase	O
.	O
http://t.co/RPTdHt6VJP	O

Pa	PER
Kasumu	PER
prepares	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
location	O
:	O
The	O
slogan	O
,	O
‘	O
The	O
show	O
must	O
go	O
on	O
’	O
,	O
appears	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
driving	O
force	O
b	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/qWVkAj8O94	O

@	PER
anghami	PER
rw3	O
a	O

Finished	O
watching	O
the	O
first	O
couple	O
of	O
Billy	PER
&	O
Mandy	PER
seasons	O
nonetheless	O
(	O
save	O
Jacked-	O
Up	O
Halloween	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
still	O
totally	O
dig	O
this	O
show	O
!	O

OH	O
MAN	O
.	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
read	O
Zadrogas	PER
book	O
.	O
Stress	O
😓	O
.	O

Oli	PER

@kultvnutri	O
HOLLY	O
MACLKERELLLLL	O
CHILDRENNNN	O

Took	O
me	O
sometime	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
I	O
am	O
strong	O
💪	O

@	PER
CipredthAyu	PER
copo	O
"	O
.	O
.	O
sabar	O
ae	O
wess	O
.	O
.	O

*	O
RETWEET	O
*	O
http://t.co/OIzQnnoSHE	O
like	O
the	O
page	O
for	O
new	O
followers	O
*	O
RETWEET	O
*	O
Thanks	O
For	O
the	O
Support	O

March	O
new	O
home	O
sales	O
plunge	O
14	O
.	O
5	O
%	O
http://t.co/7pdSuXrHoV	O

Me	O
and	O
@	PER
amberrnickkolee	PER
are	O
FINALLY	O
watching	O
last	O
nights	O
pretty	O
little	O
liars	O
episode	O
lol	O
😂	O
🅰	O

BANGING	O
Robin	PER
Thicke	PER
And	O
Paula	PER
Patton	PER
’	O
s	O
Son	O
Involved	O
In	O
Car	O
Crash	O
:	O
GistReelJust	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/vdwcFdeDqG	O
KEEP	O
IT	O
REAL	O

27	O
dead	O
,	O
109	O
hurt	O
in	O
China	LOC
rail	O
station	O
attack	O
:	O
report	O
:	O
Stabbing	O
attacks	O
at	O
a	O
Chinese	LOC
train	O
station	O
late	O
Satur	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/vOjPc2u1h9	O

I	O
usually	O
do	O
n't	O
like	O
tall	O
guys	O
but	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
@	PER
kburton_25	PER
thoooooo	O
🙌	O

RT	O
@	PER
JohnDelfsound	PER
:	O
N	O
to	O
the	O
Y	O
to	O
the	O
C	O
http://t.co/T9fyOUDzaO	O

New	O
BBM	O
pin	O
:	O
#BBMme	O
PIN	O
:	O
7	O
A	O
72	O
C	O
3	O
D	O
2	O
http://t.co/j4vt1UbsKd	O

Lydia	PER
's	O
been	O
complaining	O
,	O
ca	O
n't	O
imagine	O
when	O
she	O
officially	O
gets	O
her	O
braces	O
.	O
She	O
definitely	O
wo	O
n't	O
handle	O
it	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O

Weetabix	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
addiction	O
:	O
"	O
)	O

Your	O
colorful	O
imagination	O
is	O
flowing	O
strong	O
today	O
,	O
making	O
it	O
d	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
More	O
for	O
Cancer	O
http://t.co/L1tbFGgC4h	O

Signed	O
Western	LOC
Germany	LOC
Gold	O
Link	O
Bracelet	O
Jewelry	O
http://t.co/zEYBV8r2jh	O

RT	O
@OnePerfectShot	O
:	O
Released	O
32	O
years	O
ago	O
today	O
:	O
E	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
THE	O
EXTRA-TERRESTRIAL	O
(	O
1982	O
)	O
DoP	O
:	O
Allen	PER
Daviau	PER
|	O
Dir	O
:	O
Steven	PER
Spielberg	PER
http://t.co/jZ…	O

So	O
,	O
I	O
just	O
had	O
to	O
fire	O
someone	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Keep	O
in	O
mind	O
I	O
'm	O
not	O
a	O
supervisor	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
a	O
supervisor	O
"	O
yeah	O
go	O
ahead	O
and	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
"	O
WTF	O

Time	O
for	O
reading	O
#tfios	O
💓	O
http://t.co/XQ1gzzXjQc	O

RT	O
@	PER
StealHisHeart	PER
:	O
Do	O
n't	O
just	O
say	O
it	O
,	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Actions	O
will	O
always	O
speak	O
louder	O
than	O
words	O
.	O

"	O
@	PER
rxdioactv	PER
:	O
"	O
@	PER
indietaylors	PER
:	O
obama	PER
and	O
the	O
wanted	O
oH	O
http://t.co/BvPPJymCqP	O
"	O
calum	PER
hood	PER
and	O
miley	PER
cyrus	PER
omg	O
no	O
"	O
acacia	PER
brinley	PER
&	O
lana	PER
del	PER
ray	PER

“	O
@	PER
CollegeGameDay	PER
:	O
#SEC	ORG
West	O
Order	O
of	O
Finish	O
(	O
Media	O
)	O
:	O
1	O
.	O
Alabama	ORG
6	O
.	O
Texas	ORG
A	ORG
&	ORG
M	ORG
"	O
Is	O
this	O
where	O
we	O
hear	O
that	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
SEC	ORG
West	O
is	O
1	O
in	O
Big	O
12	O
?	O

i	O
have	O
an	O
obsession	O
with	O
online	O
shopping	O
&	O
this	O
is	O
bad	O

@	PER
ljhsen	PER
did	O
you	O
not	O
hear	O
at	O
the	O
christening	O
?	O
Natalia	PER
&	O
David	PER
are	O
expecting	O
!	O
!	O
Due	O
Jan	O
2015	O
!	O
Ps	O
that	O
's	O
news	O
I	O
can	O
share	O
;)	O
xx	O

7	O
reasons	O
we	O
can	O
’	O
t	O
wait	O
for	O
Star	O
Wars	O
:	O
Episode	O
VII	O
http://t.co/Oe38zUqDsb	O

Only	O
One	O
by	O
BoA	ORG
—	O
https://t.co/d2hRgVo7eO	O

Happy	O
birthday	O
to	O
my	O
main	O
man	O
@	PER
ScooterMcGavin8	PER
#growingup	O
#	O
19	O

@	PER
UebertAngel	PER
They	O
are	O
after	O
our	O
destruction	O

@	PER
exotarako	PER

My	O
charger	O
gave	O
up	O
on	O
me	O
already	O
😭	O
💔	O

America	LOC
's	O
NPR	ORG
segment	O
on	O
the	O
Aussie	LOC
Version	O
of	O
"	O
Rake	O
"	O
t	O
'	O
other	O
day	O
:	O
http://t.co/HmfkqRvg1H	O

RT	O
@	PER
TarynLynn24	PER
:	O
Pretty	O
sad	O
how	O
I	O
feel	O
like	O
I	O
'm	O
gonna	O
go	O
crazy	O
right	O
now	O
staying	O
home	LOC
one	O
night	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
.	O
😅	O

Que	O
fiera	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
*	O
_	O
*	O

June	O
11	O
please	O
hurry	O
the	O
fuck	O
up	O
!	O

RT	O
@	ORG
ForeignDesigns	ORG
:	O
Do	O
n't	O
take	O
nothing	O
for	O
granted	O

RT	O
@googlenexus	O
:	O
When	O
you	O
buy	O
a	O
#Nexus	O
device	O
from	O
@	ORG
GooglePlay	ORG
in	O
US	LOC
,	O
we	O
can	O
help	O
you	O
recycle	O
your	O
old	O
electronics	O
.	O
Happy	O
#EarthDay!	LOC
http	O
:	O
/	O
…	O

You	O
're	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
mood	O
to	O
be	O
pushed	O
around	O
today	O
;	O
you	O
have	O
bee	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
More	O
for	O
Scorpio	O
http://t.co/BApUjxjilo	O

RT	O
@	PER
MrDinglePopples	PER
:	O
taemin	PER
always	O
rocks	O
airport	O
fashion	O
XD	O
<	O
333	O
http://t.co/JpvFVfIFDF	O

“	O
@	PER
DerekNichols0	PER
:	O
Read	O
this	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
My	O
14	O
year	O
old	O
brother	O
wrote	O
this	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Crazyyyy	O
http://t.co/GzG2zClQUT	O
�?	O
cool	O
afffff	O

@Its_E_Bxtches	O
I	O
bet	O
you	O
did	O
hot	O
ass	O
.	O

Ahhhh	O
My	O
Hand	O
Sleep	O

RT	O
@AwkwardGoogle	O
:	O
Do	O
n't	O
burn	O
your	O
opportunities	O
for	O
a	O
temporary	O
comfort	O
.	O
.	O
!	O
http://t.co/x6HWKRnXtY	O

NEED	O
http://t.co/XomcqysJhu	O

Have	O
MH	O
370	O
parts	O
washed	O
ashore	O
?	O
Western	LOC
Australia	LOC
to	O
examine	O
unidentified	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/czEbxG46Fs	O
#WhereIsTheFuckingPlane.	O
com	O
#MH370	O

RT	O
@xxKaylaaaaa	O
:	O
I	O
'll	O
stop	O
fucking	O
with	O
someone	O
like	O
I	O
did	O
n't	O
even	O
know	O
they	O
existed	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

2	O
new	O
unfollowers	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
.	O
Via	O
http://t.co/BxOYObpjg7	O

http://t.co/eyCtv3kA8E	O
hahahaha	O
eventually	O
grow	O
followers	O

RT	O
@ari_SOMBRERO	O
:	O
NEBZ	O
spring	O
game	O
at	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Hawks	ORG
.	O
May	O
or	O
may	O
not	O
streak	O
the	O
field	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
minutes	O
in	O
#jk	O
#proudalum	O
#SGP	O

RT	O
@	PER
sampottorff	PER
:	O
Now	O
I	O
live	O
alone	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
have	O
anyone	O
telling	O
me	O
no	O
it	O
's	O
not	O
as	O
fun	O

RT	O
@sicfallacy	O
:	O
Kalau	O
opinionated	O
student	O
TESL	O
claim	O
jadi	O
apa	O
lak	O
?	O
The	O
guardian	O
of	O
English	O
language	O
madefaker	O
like	O
a	O
sir	O
?	O

@	PER
OneArmWonder	PER
@	PER
annecreaton	PER
http://t.co/eUnNg6Ofd4	O

“	O
@JoakiCoa	O
:	O
You	O
and	O
I	O
http://t.co/Ysn34FhkFw	O
�?	O

@	PER
iamseifzahran	PER
american	O
hustle	O
not	O
nominated	O
:D	O

A	O
life	O
and	O
legacy	O
of	O
service	O
:	O
Pat	PER
Tillman	PER
continues	O
to	O
change	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
10	O
years	O
after	O
his	O
death	O
http://t.co/ndMfk9Z9Ze	O
@	PER
redd_dragons	PER

RT	O
@FactsOfSchool	O
:	O
just	O
imagine	O
how	O
great	O
life	O
would	O
be	O
if	O
pizza	O
made	O
u	O
skinny	O

RT	O
@	PER
TommyRealNiggaa	PER
:	O
When	O
bae	O
havent	O
hit	O
you	O
up	O
all	O
day	O
http://t.co/bfpw5ay7mO	O

RT	O
@	PER
NoniNurhayati_	PER
:	O
Something	O
real	O
,	O
baby	O
!	O
[	O
pic	O
]	O
—	O
https://t.co/tfH3LjPhgf	O

You	O
're	O
more	O
than	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
someone	O
who	O
presents	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
More	O
for	O
Libra	O
http://t.co/VQIog69oy3	O

Unexpected	O
disruptions	O
at	O
work	O
can	O
create	O
surprising	O
opportuni	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
More	O
for	O
Virgo	O
http://t.co/KfFTIVKp5q	O

@	PER
dougiefischer	PER
HAHA	O
HELL	O
NO	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
1	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
months	O
of	O
training	O
to	O
get	O
there	O
.	O
Next	O
?	O
Pull	O
ups	O
.	O
LOL	O

@	PER
hoopaman18	PER
nope	O

#News:	O
The	O
Champions	O
'	O
#JuveX3	O
social	O
media	O
celebrations	O
!	O
:	O
Here	O
's	O
how	O
the	O
Bianconeri	ORG
players	O
themselves	O
celebra	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/qEPeYH1osO	O

So	O
far	O
I	O
have	O
2	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
semester	O
�?	O

“	O
@	PER
rubymariereyna	PER
:	O
this	O
year	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
a	O
lot	O
about	O
the	O
people	O
around	O
me	O
.	O
from	O
who	O
's	O
real	O
💯	O
who	O
's	O
fake	O
😒	O
and	O
who	O
I	O
can	O
trust	O
👌	O
�?	O
preachhhh	O
🙌	O

@	PER
Eathan__Neace	PER
I	O
never	O
sleep	O
?	O

I	O
posted	O
a	O
new	O
photo	O
to	O
Facebook	ORG
http://t.co/rihOL1uBvY	O

RT	O
@	PER
NateCaldwell4	PER
:	O
Happy	O
Birthday	O
to	O
one	O
if	O
my	O
closer	O
friends	O
!	O
@	PER
lcerrone5	PER

Jibo	ORG
Family	O
Friendly	O
Robot	O
Aims	O
To	O
Give	O
Artificial	O
Intelligence	O
A	O
Cutesy	O
Face	O
http://t.co/rxLvHrfOjQ	O

RT	O
@Why__P	O
:	O
f	O

Aint	O
sparing	O
you	O
bitches	O
🙅	O

After	O
a	O
great	O
week	O
training	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
finish	O
it	O
off	O
with	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
sledging	O
!	O
@	ORG
AmbitionRacing	ORG
http://t.co/NrCGnWk68h	O

There	O
just	O
does	O
n't	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
enough	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
to	O
connec	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
More	O
for	O
Leo	O
http://t.co/3WD3hWMr0W	O

@	PER
Annabel2010	PER
Lol	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
tweet	O
when	O
that	O
's	O
done	O
#stilltouring	O

Bringing	O
an	O
etch	O
a	O
sketch	O
to	O
school	O
instead	O
of	O
an	O
ipad	O
.	O
Idea	O
by	O
@	PER
Spencer_Jones_	PER

RT	O
@	PER
ItsJColeNC	PER
:	O
He	O
is	O
the	O
real	O
MVP	O
http://t.co/MGE1gApS8X	O

@null	O
784307689	O

@	PER
Roy_Cam	PER
That	O
is	O
a	O
ridiculous	O
statement	O
.	O
Of	O
course	O
you	O
can	O
pretend	O
to	O
be	O
Christian	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
do	O
.	O

@	PER
saarescue	PER
omg	O
that	O
's	O
wonderful	O
news	O
!	O
!	O
Well	O
done	O
dexter	PER
!	O
Xx	O

Some	O
twitts	O
fly	O
after	O
all	O
.	O
Ask	O
urself	O
what	O
u	O
have	O
done	O
to	O
advanced	O
urlife	O
since	O
January	O
1	O
of	O
2014	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

and	O
tomorrow	O
.	O

@FlTNESS	O
Right	O
on	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

Ready	O
for	O
the	O
#Rangers	ORG
game	O
to	O
start	O
already	O
.	O
Let	O
's	O
get	O
this	O
sweep	O
!	O

@	PER
SabrinaSoria_	PER
:p	O

Put	O
some	O
mineral	O
oil	O
on	O
my	O
fretboard	O
.	O
So	O
luxurious	O
.	O

@	PER
jhopekr	PER
WHAT	O
WEHRE	O

@	PER
mitchell_bodden	PER
looking	O
forward	O
to	O
it	O

Ima	O
Tell	O
Yo	O
Ass	O
If	O
I	O
Been	O
lurking	O
On	O
Yo	O
Shit	O
Or	O
Not	O
.	O
Ai	O
n't	O
No	O
Shame	O
In	O
My	O
Game	O

Yupp	O
@iam_stitches	O
:	O
7	O
:	O
1	O
abi	O
?	O
😂	O
“	O
@_OfficialAgent_	O
syfy	O
_	O
:	O
FIFA	ORG
ranks	O
BRAZIL	ORG
7th	O
and	O
Germany	ORG
1st	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
so	O
shrewd	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O
�?	O
�?	O

@	PER
TheNickAlbright	PER
haha	O
o	O
a	O
shit	O
but	O
remember	O
it	O
was	O
dome	O
chick	O

Feeling	O
so	O
lazy	O
today	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
so	O
many	O
chores	O
!	O
Ahhhhhhh	O

Iranian	O
students	O
are	O
inquiring	O
trendy	O
chinese	O
agrarianism	O
.	O
:	O
FqtFdcH	O

@	PER
hosizora1101	PER
http://t.co/Usyot8AEn0	O

@	ORG
PoliticaILine	ORG
@whoseowen	O
Typical	O
of	O
the	O
RW	O
hawks	O
(	O
to	O
paraphrase	O
a	O
line	O
from	O
"	O
Patton	PER
"	O
)	O
:	O
Our	O
blood	O
,	O
their	O
guts	O
.	O

@	PER
nigellymilk	PER
HAHAHHAA	O
SIYA	O
NGA	O
PI	O
100	O
KO	O
NAKAKAINIS	O

@	PER
CalmWooTits	PER
ahh	O
ok	O
so	O
with	O
the	O
suram	O
myung	O
(	O
?	O
)	O
Not	O
the	O
bright	O
myung	O
right	O
?	O
Okk	O
!	O
Gonna	O
finish	O
it	O
by	O
tmr	O
morning	O
/	O
bc	O
holiday	O
/	O
ditunggu	O
yaa	O

.	O
.	O
.	O
Until	O
its	O
flow	O
is	O
interrupted	O
.	O

RT	O
@finessinking	O
:	O
“	O
@	PER
_thatbxtchCourt	PER
:	O
Death	O
is	O
really	O
hitting	O
home	O
I	O
'm	O
preparing	O
myself	O
�?	O
�?	O
💯	O

I	O
got	O
a	O
reward	O
:	O
Friendly	O
in	O
BigBusiness	O
Deluxe	O
for	O
Android	ORG
http://t.co/j2CKwcCkfh	O
#Androidgames	O
#Android	O
#Gameinsight	O

#UGG	ORG
#auction	O
NEW	O
UGG	ORG
Australia	LOC
Men	O
ROCKVILLE	O
II	O
Motorcycle	O
/	O
Casual	O
leather	O
Boot	O
US	O
11	O
.	O
5	O
Dune	O
http://t.co/ueU95Z3U9f	O

#	O
3	O
:	O
Crocs	ORG
Kids	O
Handle	O
It	O
Rain	O
Boot	O
Wellingtons	O
http://t.co/fZCjaixIQO	O
Crocs	ORG
Kids	O
Handle	O
It	O
Rain	O
Boot	O
Wellingto	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/f3LkFQg5r6	O

RT	O
@	ORG
WildflowersHQ	ORG
:	O
Wildflowers	ORG
on	O
Tour	O
:	O
DAY	O
1	O
-	O
BRISTOL	LOC
!	O
First	O
stop	O
@	LOC
LouisianaVenue	LOC
,	O
look	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
red	O
van	O
near	O
you	O
!	O
#letitgotour	O
http	O
:	O
/	O
…	O

@	PER
thekeyisyou	PER
come	O
on	O
keypunch	O
!	O
You	O
can	O
do	O
this	O
!	O
💪	O

@	PER
yungleana	PER
that	O
's	O
pretty	O
sick	O
yo	O

What	O
if	O
technology	O
stagnated	O
here	O
?	O

"	O
Sometimes	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
to	O
help	O
a	O
person	O
is	O
to	O
not	O
help	O
him	O
/	O
her	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
"	O

@null	O
http://t.co/iamNn7PDNk	O

Vanilla	LOC
Islands	LOC
at	O
the	O
Arabian	LOC
Travel	LOC
Market	LOC
in	O
Dubai	LOC
:	O
Rose-	PER
Marie	PER
Hoareau	PER
the	O
Director	O
of	O
Marketing	O
at	O
the	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/OJCZbvkPvq	O

RT	O
@	ORG
OneProductionSG	ORG
:	O
#FTHX	O
Are	O
you	O
all	O
counting	O
down	O
to	O
FTISLAND	ORG
concert	O
!	O
5	O
more	O
days	O
and	O
FTISLAND	ORG
will	O
be	O
in	O
Singapore	LOC
to	O
see	O
all	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http	O
…	O

Sharing	O
:	O
http://t.co/Nt1vtnI9lp	O

RT	O
@	ORG
reviewjournal	ORG
:	O
Fla	LOC
.	O
man	O
files	O
class-action	O
lawsuit	O
over	O
receiving	O
text	O
msgs	O
.	O
from	O
Las	LOC
Vegas	LOC
show	O
.	O
http://t.co/KeqJhnHbdY	O

@	PER
Alexissssss_J	PER
dont	O
talk	O
to	O
me	O
then	O

@	PER
lexibraicovich	PER
@	PER
gwynnharris	PER
there	O
is	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
lex	PER

J	O
's	O
on	O
my	O
feet	O
J	O
's	O
on	O
my	O
feet	O
👟	O
💙	O
#babybao	O
#	O
23	O
#handsome	O
http://t.co/2SH5OaQO8p	O

Now	O
Playing	O
:	O
Nicky	PER
Romero	PER
ft	O
Calvin	PER
Harris	PER
-	O
Iron	O
[	O
8	O
:3	O
34	O
pm	O
]	O

I	O
will	O
bring	O
@	PER
imerikapotato	PER
because	O
we	O
really	O
really	O
want	O
to	O
see	O
Taylor	PER
Swift	PER
so	O
badly	O
.	O
#SpinnrTaylorSwift	PER
747	O

Once	O
upon	O
a	O
time	O
nobody	O
gave	O
a	O
fuck	O

Trying	O
too	O
hard	O
is	O
not	O
good	O
for	O
you	O

RT	O
@	ORG
amnesty	ORG
:	O
2	O
weeks	O
too	O
long	O
!	O
Tell	O
Nigerian	O
officials	O
to	O
do	O
everything	O
to	O
#BringBackOurGirls	O
now	O
:	O
http://t.co/Zhu9a5MQUZ	O
http://t.co/zAbj…	O

RT	O
@	ORG
Dis_ShowMoneyy	ORG
:	O
Ready	O
to	O
hit	O
the	O
house	O

RT	O
@	PER
kimyixing_	PER
:	O
Jongin	O
reaction	O
to	O
new	O
chanyeol	ORG
smart	O
watch	O
unique	O
http://t.co/9VVK89G2c9	O

@	ORG
Radio702	ORG
how	O
far	O
can	O
parties	O
campaign	O
outside	O
vote	O
stations	O
?	O
ward	LOC
90	LOC
voting	LOC
station	LOC
32960853	O
there	O
is	O
ANC	O
tent	O
just	O
outside	O
the	O
station	O
.	O

@	PER
____Rik	PER
@	PER
Liljay_UpNext00	PER
@	PER
ChiefKeef	PER
the	O
nigga	O
jay	PER
diss	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
and	O
wish	O
chief	PER
wud	O
do	O
some	O
but	O
sosa	O
real	O
butnotwhenitcometojay	O

Art	O
Style	O
:	O
Techno	O
|	O
Selection	O
Sorted	O
Night	O
[	O
Part	O
1	O
]	O
:	O
DVNT	ORG
[	O
2014	O
.	O
02	O
.	O
26	O
]	O
https://t.co/tzLag2E0bW	O

RT	ORG
@	PER
PerezHilton	PER
:	O
#JustinBieber	PER
&	O
#SelenaGomez	PER
Are	O
BACK	O
ON	O
?	O
!	O
Biebsy	PER
Instagrams	O
THIS	O
Sweet	O
Pic	O
Then	O
Deletes	O
It	O
!	O
http://t.co/CsSvl7QCGv	O

@	PER
DavDoc95	PER
I	O
'm	O
off	O
�?	O

Yeah	O
.	O
*	O
tickles	O
@	PER
mlp_Perla	PER
behind	O
the	O
ear	O
*	O

@	PER
elynElina	PER
oh	O
dah	O
buat	O
pc	O
keee	O
.	O
Patut	O
xde	O
intern	O
.	O
Thanks	O
elyn	PER
!	O
;)	O

RT	O
@	PER
KibaliMoreithi	PER
:	O
I	O
MIGHT	O
be	O
on	O
TV	O
and	O
Radio	O
starting	O
tomorrow	O
*	O
Faints	O
*	O
Time	O
to	O
finally	O
put	O
that	O
communications	O
degree	O
to	O
good	O
use	O
.	O

@	ORG
MLBFanCave	ORG

RT	O
@	PER
_hernameisANDY	PER
:	O
“	O
@	PER
Blues4_Nina	PER
:	O
Do	O
n't	O
temp	O
me	O
,	O
just	O
act	O
right	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
temp	O
me	O
.	O
�?	O
#itcouldallbesosimple	O

Gerrard	PER
's	O
shots	O
are	O
impeccable	O

@	LOC
_OhioGrown	LOC
I	O
saw	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
@BewareoDarkess	O
concert	O
and	O
waved	O
at	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
forgot	O
my	O
face	O
.	O
.	O
)	O
:	O
and	O
looked	O
away	O
.	O

@	ORG
ComicBook_Movie	ORG
We	O
are	O
offering	O
#XMen	O
fans	O
the	O
chance	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
#DOFP	O
cast	O
their	O
questions	O
via	O
Skype	O
!	O
http://t.co/ki9KqZlwd6	O

RT	O
@	PER
justinbieber	PER
:	O
i	O
dont	O
plan	O
on	O
ever	O
losing	O
any	O
fans	O
.	O
young	O
or	O
old	O
.	O
only	O
gaining	O
more	O
and	O
more	O
respect	O
.	O
MJ	PER
never	O
left	O
the	O
kids	O
he	O
just	O
gre	O
…	O

Everything	O
is	O
gonna	O
be	O
alright	O
#EnriqueIglesias	PER

Mill	PER
Will	PER
Ate	O
It	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O

RT	O
@	PER
SCatsx	PER
:	O
http://t.co/6miZ8vLJSW	O

RT	O
@dailyteenwords	O
:	O
My	O
feelings	O
?	O
Yes	O
it	O
's	O
okay	O
,	O
its	O
like	O
nobody	O
cares	O
anymore	O
either	O
.	O

http://t.co/Yy1OEtdwIp	O

@	PER
bhaydon5	PER
Sure	O
!	O
Minus	O
the	O
DSM-V	O
.	O
Not	O
going	O
to	O
"	O
read	O
"	O
that	O
one	O
.	O
Lol	O
.	O
Just	O
a	O
reference	O
book	O
for	O
grad	O
school	O
.	O
Woot	O
woot	O
!	O

The	O
6th	O
Samui	LOC
Bike	O
Week	O
ready	O
to	O
roar	O
into	O
life	O
http://t.co/kcvW3ZfrWA	O
http://t.co/Pq2vzDWsQ7	O

@	PER
apandolf	PER
TY	PER
:-)	O

We	O
'll	O
be	O
a	O
dream	O
💋	O

@	PER
Halpacino77	PER
@	PER
Paulmcgrath5	PER
shes	O
just	O
tryin	O
to	O
be	O
kind	O
mate	O
:	O
-	O
(	O

Who	O
's	O
Gladis	PER
?	O
?	O
?	O
Just	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
Ridgeway	LOC
Arms	LOC
,	O
uncovered	O
the	O
black	O
board	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
spooky	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/X1bafqL9PT	O

Stressed	O
,	O
exhuasted	O
and	O
annoyed	O
.	O
Yey	O
.	O

Out	O
of	O
My	O
League	O
-	O
Fitz	ORG
and	ORG
the	ORG
Tantrums	ORG
#nowplaying	O

Udh	O
gak	O
fokuss	O
.	O
_	O
.	O

RT	O
@	PER
ashtondruwhaley	PER
:	O
Hey	O
,	O
@	PER
CassidyWalden	PER
,	O
do	O
n't	O
tell	O
Jesse	PER
or	O
Jaden	PER
,	O
but	O
you	O
're	O
my	O
favorite	O

RT	O
@Greek1directio	O
:	O
@	PER
Luke5SOS	PER
@	PER
iNiallsSmilee_	PER
i	O
'm	O
gonna	O
watch	O
this	O
movie	O
today	O
!	O
!	O
1	O

“	O
@TheSwaveeGod	O
:	O
Do	O
not	O
break	O
the	O
heart	O
that	O
loves	O
you	O
!	O
�?	O

bgd	O
wooow	O
:D	O
http://t.co/djpTLZ63uv	O

Kin	PER
give	O
out	O
DNA	O
samples	O
as	O
divers	O
recover	O
bodies	O
from	O
South	LOC
Korean	LOC
ferry	O
-	O
JINDO	LOC
,	O
South	LOC
Korea	LOC
(	O
CNN	O
)	O
—	O
Relatives	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/H0zKj0sPQr	O

RT	O
@	PER
Taraa_x0	PER
:	O
Hate	O
waking	O
up	O
and	O
not	O
knowing	O
what	O
to	O
wear	O
😅	O

@	PER
justinbieber	PER
Happy	O
Birthday	O
Jay	PER
,	O
We	O
'll	O
always	O
be	O
here	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
always	O
be	O
here	O
supporting	O
you	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
forget	O
that	O
we	O
love	O
you	O
Justin	PER
💜	O
💜	O
17	O

@AbrarUlHaqPK	O
http://t.co/TDgAojPLJo	O

At	O
the	O
Rail	O
beer	O
dinner	O
March	O
24th	O
http://t.co/y9TLXKo5l5	O

How	O
can	O
you	O
want	O
so	O
much	O
attention	O
?	O
#slag	O
#getalife	O

@	PER
LozDawney	PER
We	O
're	O
still	O
working	O
on	O
it	O
Loz	PER
&	O
it	O
's	O
likely	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
those	O
works	O
that	O
you	O
're	O
seeing	O
different	O
experiences	O
>	O
J	O

Photo	O
:	O
http://t.co/DVy4My3d6Y	O

my	O
heart	O
breaks	O
alittle	O
when	O
I	O
hear	O
your	O
name	O
.	O
💔	O

Getting	O
some	O
studio	O
foam	O
and	O
new	O
equipment	O
.	O
#music	O
#production	O
#monitors	O
#foam	O
#interface	O
#guitarplayers	O
http://t.co/fZNpxkfDXP	O

@	PER
GrantColl	PER
@	PER
BhoyEddie	PER
It	O
is	O
only	O
200	O
out	O
of	O
1600	O
.	O
Stores	O
in	O
mainly	O
muslim	O
areas	O
,	O
with	O
mainly	O
muslim	O
staff	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
and	O
mainly	O
muslim	O
customers	O
.	O

@	PER
120Noam	PER
ofirvered4	O

Wherever	O
you	O
go	O
,	O
no	O
matter	O
what	O
the	O
weather	O
,	O
always	O
bring	O
your	O
own	O
sunshine	O
☀	O
#GM	ORG
WORLD	O
!	O
!	O
💋	O
http://t.co/WaqrSvrreK	O

RT	O
@	PER
AnnaBelleBTW	PER
:	O
I	O
be	O
sleeping	O
so	O
good	O
until	O
it	O
's	O
time	O
to	O
wake	O
up	O
😫	O

RT	O
@CallMeMegzzz	O
:	O
Honestly	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
decent	O
night	O
of	O
sleep	O

£	O
25	O
Free	O
Bet	O
for	O
new	O
customers	O
from	O
TitanBet	ORG
http://t.co/cx2JhLhxCn	O

@Hz__22	O
+	O
1	O

#news	O
Boogeymen	O
and	O
shady	O
deals	O
define	O
spin	O
for	O
Senate	ORG
:	O
WASHINGTON	LOC
(	O
AP	O
)	O
—	O
To	O
hear	O
party	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/CCDbzHaCxD	O
http://t.co/6Si3P3zzT5	O

RT	O
@	PER
JamesEmeryWhite	PER
:	O
The	O
slowest	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
natural	O
,	O
emotional	O
recharges	O
tend	O
to	O
be	O
much	O
more	O
God-honoring	O
than	O
the	O
fast	O
,	O
articifical	O
hits	O
w	O
…	O

Why	O
were	O
Burger	ORG
King	ORG
's	O
chicken	O
fries	O
ever	O
discontinued	O
?	O
?	O
They	O
were	O
the	O
only	O
good	O
thing	O
there	O
!	O

Idk	O
why	O
in	O
fascinated	O
by	O
Greek	O
mythology	O

@	PER
BoomerandCarton	PER
forsure	O
not	O
tiki	PER
,	O
he	O
trashed	O
the	O
giants	ORG
b4	O
we	O
won	O
in	O
07	O
.	O
Spags	PER
or	O
coughlin	PER
.	O

RT	O
@	PER
_AlexHirsch	PER
:	O
Soos	PER
has	O
his	O
own	O
Home	O
Repair	O
show	O
?	O
This	O
is	O
an	O
unsettling	O
development	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
https://t.co/dC1jjDiHfW	O

Spend	O
a	O
worthy	O
minute	O
to	O
read	O
this	O
.	O
#mindfulness	O
#zen	O
http://t.co/lXh2hMqyd7	O

RT	O
@	PER
LOHANTHONY	PER
:	O
sacrificing	O
sleep	O
for	O
netflix	ORG
has	O
just	O
become	O
a	O
routine	O

I	O
feel	O
like	O
being	O
grumpy	O
today	O
,	O
just	O
because	O
I	O
can	O
.	O

Piriapolisssss	LOC

omg	O
#FanArmy	O
goes	O
to	O
#RihannaNavy	PER
#iHeartAwards	ORG
http://t.co/wtDILQy4VQ	O

Single	O
and	O
ready	O
to	O
mingle	O
.	O
She	O
's	O
out	O
there	O
waiting	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
http://t.co/qqARNffybr	ORG

Lameeee	O

“	O
@	ORG
disneywords	ORG
:	O
Even	O
miracles	O
take	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
.	O
–	O
Fairy	PER
Godmother	PER
(	O
Cinderella	PER
)	O
�?	O

RT	O
@	PER
maddz2B	PER
:	O
ily	O
@	PER
The_Spermatron	PER

Crawling	O
back	O
under	O
my	O
rock	O
before	O
I	O
explode	O

RT	O
@	PER
niaIlporn	PER
:	O
FOLLOW	O
TRICK	O
$	O
rt	O
$	O
follow	O
me	O
and	O
@	PER
vogueclarice	PER
$	O
follow	O
everyone	O
who	O
rts	O
$	O
gain	O
!	O
fav	O
if	O
you	O
wanna	O
be	O
mentioned	O
(	O
mbf	O
)	O

RT	O
@FuckFeeIings	O
:	O
I	O
love	O
my	O
mother	O
no	O
matter	O
what	O
.	O

[	O
Captured	O
by	O
B	O
2	O
ST-VN	O
]	O
140611	O
NOW-Trouble	ORG
Maker	ORG
@	O
Jungbudae	LOC
Festival	LOC
#	O
29	O
-	O
30	O
-	O
31	O
@	PER
B2UTYMAKASSAR	PER
Owner	O
of	O
photos	O
on	O
pics	O
http://t.co/ACWpujSNVz	O

RT	O
@	PER
MahoganyLOX	PER
:	O
I	O
was	O
watching	O
you	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
thinking	O
I	O
had	O
ya	O
…	O
How	O
was	O
I	O
ever	O
so	O
dumb	O
?	O
🎶	O
🎶	O
🎶	O

You	O
're	O
far	O
away	O
@	PER
Louis_Tomlinson	PER
but	O
I	O
feel	O
you	O
near	O
me	O
💞	O
Please	O
,	O
follow	O
me	O
and	O
make	O
me	O
the	O
happiest	O
girl	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Love	O
you	O
,	O
honey	O
☀	O
�?	O
801	O

Check	O
out	O
these	O
top	O
10	O
science	O
fiction	O
authors	O
!	O
http://t.co/V3KZivAEqr	O

RT	O
@	PER
WrightLaRoche	PER
:	O
Take	O
a	O
look	O
at	O
this	O
great	O
site	O
!	O
Author	O
@	PER
ZoeSaadia	PER
writes	O
about	O
Aztec	ORG
!	O
http://t.co/t3hvaO6vp5	O
#AuthorRT	O

RT	O
@	PER
jennettemccurdy	PER
:	O
RT	O
for	O
a	O
million	O
bucks	O
(	O
just	O
kidding	O
,	O
a	O
follow	O
)	O

http://t.co/0I3tpWXgQk	O

♪	O
All	O
the	O
kids	O
have	O
always	O
known	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
emperor	O
wears	O
no	O
clothes	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
bow	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
anyway	O
,	O
its	O
better	O
than	O
being	O
alone	O
♪	O

My	O
favorite	O
upperclassmen	O

RT	O
@	PER
rileystarkk	PER
:	O
hmm	O
what	O
do	O
I	O
wear	O
tomorrow	O

RT	O
@	PER
AustinMahone	PER
:	O
Having	O
a	O
meeting	O
with	O
my	O
brothers	O
discussing	O
our	O
next	O
big	O
move	O
💰	O

#houserules	O
#slaughterhousemusic	O
goes	O
hard	O
@	PER
JoeBudden	PER
@RoyceDaFive9	O

Do	O
n't	O
forget	O
we	O
are	O
hiring	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
team	O
of	O
people	O
to	O
add	O
to	O
our	O
@	ORG
sensewhere	ORG
crew	O
http://t.co/nfbW5kTZs9	O
#jobsearch	O
#technology	O

@	PER
PogalJoners	PER
@	ORG
GreenpeaceUK	ORG
You	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
floundering	O
on	O
this	O
issue	O
,	O
Paul	PER
#yeeeeeeeees	O

http://t.co/HV4OKinhAF	O

RT	O
@	PER
KicchaSudeep	PER
:	O
Dad	O
turns	O
75	O
today	O
.	O
.	O
Need	O
all	O
ur	O
wshs	O
n	O
prayers	O
fr	O
many	O
more	O
years	O
of	O
him	O
wth	O
us	O
.	O
.	O
Happy	O
bday	O
Appa	PER
.	O
.	O
Makin	O
me	O
Strong	O
is	O
th	O
b	O
…	O

Shoutout	O
to	O
@	PER
eduardjohn18	PER
follow	O
niyo	PER
,	O
he	O
follows	O
back	O
.	O
ASK	O
.	O
:)	O

RT	O
@	ORG
PGATOUR	ORG
:	O
The	O
lone	O
water	O
hazard	O
at	O
Pinehurst	LOC
No	LOC
.	LOC
2	LOC
,	O
just	O
off	O
the	O
16th	O
tee	O
.	O
#USOpen	O
http://t.co/6GsLFh1TgZ	O

RT	O
@	PER
dukeofmuke	PER
:	O
The	O
words	O
5sos	O
and	O
nudity	O
flow	O
so	O
effortlessly	O
together	O

chanyeol	PER
is	O
enjoying	O
IG	O
so	O
much	O

@	PER
ClaudiaOlsberg	PER
you	O
have	O
said	O
it	O
in	O
like	O
every	O
tweet	O
,	O
obviously	O
am	O
x	O

Computer	O
Fixed	O
UK	LOC
:	O
You	O
can	O
get	O
LG	ORG
's	O
first	O
Chrome	O
all-in-one	O
later	O
this	O
month	O
for	O
$	O
350	O
http://t.co/un7vPsI0Ev	O

I	O
should	O
n't	O
have	O
done	O
that	O
to	O
Youngstown	LOC
last	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
apologize	O
!	O
Lol	O

RT	O
@ChemistryWorld	O
:	O
Our	O
free	O
#webinar	O
on	O
'	O
laboratory	O
health	O
&	O
safety	O
and	O
the	O
law	O
'	O
starts	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
-	O
register	O
here	O
to	O
join	O
us	O
!	O
http	O
:	O
/	O
…	O

RT	O
@	PER
TheMattEspinosa	PER
:	O
Nj	O

2	O
days	O
with	O
unforgetable	O
memories	O
(	O
{	O
}	O
)	O

@	PER
girlcallederin	PER
Is	O
that	O
the	O
long	O
haired	O
fella	O
?	O
Pretty	O
sure	O
he	O
’	O
s	O
Cornish	LOC
,	O
which	O
explains	O
the	O
rad	O
accent	O
.	O

RT	O
@	PER
awkwardposts	PER
:	O
when	O
ur	O
mom	O
turns	O
a	O
joke	O
into	O
a	O
speech	O
http://t.co/T6yrfH8XMa	O

Every	O
night	O
like	O
this	O
.	O
.	O

Wendy	LOC
's	LOC
calling	O
my	O
name	O
😭	O

Sunday	O
Salvacion	O
's	O
shooting	O
touch	O
0	O
.	O
o	O
#Shooter	O

@	PER
justinbieber	PER
Happy	O
Birthday	O
I	O
've	O
been	O
here	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
here	O
forever	O
�?�	O
�?	O
💕	O

RT	O
@	ORG
nflnetwork	ORG
:	O
10	O
hours	O
to	O
Schedule	O
Release	O
.	O
Raise	O
your	O
hand	O
(	O
or	O
RT	O
)	O
if	O
you	O
feel	O
like	O
this	O
.	O
#NFLSchedule	ORG
http://t.co/7wed88JYic	O

“	O
@	PER
TagaLPU	PER
:	O
Final	O
word	O
tonight	O
:	O
"	O
Never	O
ignore	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
loves	O
you	O
and	O
cares	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
"	O
�?	O

http://t.co/hY2E3nx3fR	O

RT	O
@	PER
LGlaurenn	PER
:	O
WHY	O
AM	O
I	O
SUCH	O
A	O
PROCRASTINATOR	O

@	PER
Harry_Styles	PER
@	PER
Real_Liam_Payne	PER
@	PER
Louis_Tomlinson	PER
@	PER
NiallOfficial	PER
@	PER
zaynmalik	PER
Today	O
it	O
´	O
s	O
my	O
birthday	O
And	O
I	O
just	O
wanna	O
your	O
congratulations	O
56	O

RT	O
@	PER
FunnyVines	PER
:	O
A	O
cat	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
door	O
during	O
a	O
French	O
TV	O
baking	O
show	O
and	O
it	O
's	O
absolutely	O
amazing	O
.	O
https://t.co/JQd3n8B5lj	O

@	PER
VamboOssy	PER
@GAMEBlackburn	O
ahhhhh	O
I	O
blame	O
old	O
age	O
memory	O
problems	O

#Team228	O
http://t.co/XNk97qThCc	ORG

@	PER
ArianaGrande	PER
just	O
to	O
remember	O
that	O
10	O
lives	O
I	O
'd	O
give	O
you	O
11	O
<	O
3	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
my	O
baby	O
♥	O
21	O

RT	O
@HistoryInPics	O
:	O
Peter	PER
Jackson	PER
with	O
the	O
cast	O
before	O
the	O
filming	O
of	O
Lord	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
http://t.co/r1fiswbEie	O

@	PER
parkerann4	PER
there	O
she	O
is	O
😘	O
gahhhh	O

Gets	O
way	O
too	O
boring	O
going	O
on	O
holiday	O
for	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
week	O
when	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
have	O
any	O
siblings	O

My	O
mom	O
is	O
the	O
best	O
�?�	O
�?	O
💪	O
�?	O

@	PER
ss_Dbz	PER
if	O
I	O
do	O
this	O
I	O
wanna	O
see	O
a	O
fireball	O
jutsu	O
shoot	O
out	O
my	O
finger	O
tips	O

Recent	O
Stats	O
=	O
1	O
Followers	O
and	O
0	O
Unfollowers	O
get	O
your	O
statistics	O
at	O
http://t.co/xykJbODyFm	O

#BOO	O
http://t.co/UmF1f1tVb4	O

http://t.co/SWelCek3IP	O

Ccleaner	O
is	O
wise	O
software	O
:	O
gks	O

@	PER
ItsMrsMoran	PER
@	PER
jenniferbeals	PER
there	O
would	O
be	O
many	O
characters	O
from	O
the	O
show	O
.	O
(	O
BTW	O
its	O
bearski	O
here	O
.	O
Another	O
alias	O
)	O
Would	O
U	O
include	O
all	O
?	O

@	PER
pattiemallette	PER
awww	O
Pattie	PER
.	O
You	O
are	O
far	O
from	O
old	O
!	O
You	O
look	O
like	O
you	O
're	O
still	O
in	O
your	O
20s	O
!	O

RT	O
@	PER
IrinaGreenVoice	PER
:	O
This	O
fragile	O
&	O
irreplaceable	O
environment	O
at	O
risk	O
of	O
a	O
catastrophic	O
oil	O
spill	O
!	O
#SaveTheArctic	LOC
>	O
http://t.co/6Il7oHk3c4	O
…	O

RT	O
@	PER
EmrgencyKittens	PER
:	O
Gave	O
the	O
cat	O
a	O
computer	O
,	O
he	O
's	O
not	O
very	O
good	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
http://t.co/ZQUNTW6Qff	O

RT	O
@	PER
hannahbolt1	PER
:	O
Fries	O
are	O
everything	O

How	O
to	O
Prolong	O
the	O
Life	O
of	O
Your	O
Toyota	ORG
Sienna	O
Sliding	O
Door	O
Cables	O
http://t.co/XO8nM8CwOn	O

Look	O
at	O
Kris	PER
new	O
hair	O

@ImAGingerMonkey	O
it	O
's	O
always	O
refreshing	O
to	O
make	O
room	O
for	O
new	O
things	O
;)	O

RT	O
@	PER
AustinFordYoung	PER
:	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
need	O
someone	O
like	O
you	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
anymore	O
.	O

@	PER
Jeffweey56	PER
lol	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
moment	O

Family	O
http://t.co/3CjLXSE8IS	O

RT	O
@PoemsPorn	O
:	O
http://t.co/Pn9M2skwlF	O

http://t.co/DCXHoN69oA	O

Sooooo	O
ready	O
for	O
summer	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

The	ORG
Vamps	ORG
-	O
Last	O
Night	O
♥	O

RT	O
@	PER
FactSoup	PER
:	O
http://t.co/OVZU131vwY	O

"	O
@	ORG
INFINITE92KIML	ORG
:	O
@	PER
jupalyeon_	PER
i	O
love	O
you	O
heh	O
"	O
i	O
love	O
you	O
too	O
woy	O

Knock	O
It	O
Off	O
!	O
Latest	O
Zombie	PER
Boy	PER
:	O
http://t.co/AMWjhubHar	O
#ZombieBoy	O
#webcomic	O
#voodoo	O

RT	O
@scooterbraun	O
:	O
Happy	O
20th	O
birthday	O
@	PER
justinbieber	PER
!	O
See	O
u	O
soon	O
!	O
Been	O
a	O
pleasure	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
journey	O
.	O
Love	O
yah	O
http://t.co/DZCKWCM…	O

@	PER
kkatieelderr	PER
thats	O
some	O
bull	O

That	O
awkward	O
moment	O
when	O
you	O
're	O
answering	O
a	O
test	O
question	O
and	O
the	O
answer	O
is	O
so	O
ovious	O
,	O
you	O
actually	O
doubt	O
yourself	O
.	O

@	PER
emmapotts_	PER
pls	O
go	O
city	O
xoxox	O

@	PER
untouchablet_	PER
that	O
's	O
mean	O

@	ORG
5SOS	ORG
and	O
I	O
bet	O
michael	PER
ate	O
most	O
of	O
if	O

@	PER
btsukjeen	PER
fans	O

Bye	O
.	O
Sleep	O

RT	O
@	ORG
TedOfficialPage	ORG
:	O
#TheMostAnnoyingThingsInLife	O
1	O
)	O
Slow	O
internet	O
connection	O
2	O
)	O
Being	O
cheated	O
3	O
)	O
Being	O
ignored	O
4	O
)	O
Being	O
replaced	O
5	O
)	O
H	O
…	O

My	O
bus	O
come	O
at	O
6	O
:3	O
38	O
i	O
got	O
out	O
the	O
shower	O
at	O
6	O
:3	O
30	O
😂	O
😂	O

@	PER
Danii_Azucena	PER
@	ORG
TheSpanishVines	ORG
hahahaha	O
that	O
is	O
too	O
cute	O
!	O
It	O
really	O
will	O
be	O
!	O
:)	O
he	O
already	O
loves	O
the	O
weekends	O
!	O

@	PER
aishimas4	PER
he	O
High	ORG
Frequency	ORG
Active	ORG
Auroral	ORG
Research	ORG
Program	ORG
(	O
HAARP	ORG
)	O
is	O
an	O
ionospheric	O
research	O
program	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
check	O
it	O
out	O
;)	O

@itsBrilliance	O
It	O
's	O
almost	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

RT	O
@	PER
Suntimes	PER
:	O
Why	O
wo	O
n't	O
more	O
challengers	O
step	O
to	O
unpopular	O
Rahm	PER
?	O
@	PER
fspielman	PER
breaks	O
it	O
down	O
:	O
money	O
,	O
city	O
woes	O
and	O
fear	O
http://t.co/mwpVHil4ND	O

#Cougar	O
#Horny	O
#Hot	O
#Housewife	O
#Mature	O
#MILF	O
http://t.co/0WmJvXkjmk	O
"	O

My	O
voice	O
is	O
gettin	O
higherrr	O
�?	O

Tancia	PER
,	O
Woman	O
from	O
Rome	LOC
,	O
41	O
years	O
http://t.co/4OfrWimEvu	O
http://t.co/d3HFf4KecB	O

RT	O
@	PER
GarethBale22	PER
:	O
No	O
@	ORG
Arsenal	ORG
,	O
@	ORG
realmadrid	ORG
do	O
n't	O
give	O
refunds	O
!	O

RT	O
@FactsGuide	O
:	O
80	O
%	O
of	O
people	O
remain	O
quiet	O
even	O
when	O
they	O
really	O
want	O
to	O
say	O
something	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
avoid	O
an	O
argument	O
with	O
someone	O
they	O
care	O
…	O

choto	O
celu	O
choto	O
:c	O

@	PER
JerSchrand	PER
Thank	O
you	O
!	O

RT	O
@	PER
dominiqueemonte	PER
:	O
its	O
scary	O
that	O
im	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
senior	O
next	O
year	O

@TheDareRising	O
If	O
you	O
guys	O
do	O
an	O
RC	O
i	O
will	O
quit	O
doing	O
the	O
FaZe	O
5	O
RC	O
and	O
do	O
yours	O
#Dare	O

RT	O
@	PER
m_ciccarone	PER
:	O
Sent	O
myself	O
a	O
"	O
good	O
job	O
on	O
not	O
dropping	O
out	O
this	O
semester	O
"	O
present	O
from	O
@belles_and_bows	O
to	O
arrive	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
exams	O
�?	O

@npomalley	O
Horror	O
!	O
!	O
How	O
un-	O
American	O
!	O
!	O
Impeach	O
him	O
now	O
!	O
!	O

RT	O
@	PER
Demyliano	PER
:	O
@	PER
michaelsvcks	PER
no	O
doubt	O
this	O
kid	O
is	O
raw	O
bro	O

RT	O
@	ORG
RadDates	ORG
:	O
a	O
rad	O
date	O
would	O
be	O
http://t.co/y7pU6Xt2Cg	O

RT	O
@jdbftasvp	O
:	O
but	O
pattie	PER
is	O
the	O
one	O
that	O
looks	O
20	O
http://t.co/Yxkp9wTLhS	O

Criminal	O
is	O
under	O
arrest	O
!	O
Fight	O
the	O
gangs	O
in	O
the	O
streets	O
of	O
London	LOC
!	O
http://t.co/yS8xe3lXO3	O
#iPad	O
#iPadGames	O
#GameInsight	O

The	O
end	O
of	O
an	O
incredible	O
journey	O
that	O
I	O
shared	O
with	O
wonderful	O
people	O
in	O
an	O
amazing	O
place	O
#	O
2014	O
#QF…	O
http://t.co/dPUDbdZRsP	O

RT	O
@	PER
TourBarCom	PER
:	O
Millennials	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
travelers	O
.	O
29	O
reasons	O
why	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
-	O
>	O
http://t.co/7nu5sgzxF2	O
#travel	O
#Millennials	O

Waiting	O
for	O
this	O
pre	O
work	O
out	O
to	O
kick	O
in	O

Tft	O
woyy	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
:*	O
{	O
}	O
<	O
3	O
@	PER
MahendraRandi	PER

We	O
do	O
have	O
a	O
favourable	O
run	O
in	O
as	O
well	O
.	O
We	O
go	O
on	O
a	O
winning	O
streak	O
and	O
those	O
above	O
draw	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
games	O
and	O
we	O
're	O
right	O
in	O
the	O
mix	O
.	O
#pnefc	ORG

FANM	PER
PA	PER
DRA	PER
MET	PER
BOUDAW	PER
ANLE	O
:	O
http://t.co/GrZxKTW5nx	O
via	O
@	ORG
YouTube	ORG

♥	O
♥	O
♥	O
@	PER
Luke5SOS	PER
Because	O
of	O
you	O
I	O
laugh	O
a	O
little	O
harder	O
,	O
cry	O
a	O
little	O
less	O
and	O
smile	O
a	O
lot	O
more	O
.	O
Can	O
I	O
please	O
have	O
a	O
follow	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
♥	O
♥	O
♥	O
x1616	O

Ah	O
parah	O

RT	O
@amthinker	O
:	O
The	O
unhappiest	O
workers	O
of	O
all	O
:	O
How	O
’	O
s	O
that	O
feminism	O
workin	O
’	O
out	O
for	O
ya	O
?	O
http://t.co/f1IUzikHX5	O
b	O

#oomf,	O
YOU	O
KNOW	O
WHAT	O
TO	O
DO	O
WITH	O
THAT	O
BIG	O
FAT	O
BUTT	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
WIGGLE	O
WIGGLE	O
WIGGLE	O
.	O

RT	ORG
@	PER
neymarsjersey	PER
:	O
Why	O
are	O
people	O
spreading	O
rumors	O
that	O
Bruna	PER
and	O
Neymar	PER
are	O
getting	O
married	O
she	O
's	O
an	O
actress	O
it	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
show	O
.	O
peop	O
…	O

Al-	ORG
Shabaab	ORG
Wants	O
Kenyans	LOC
to	O
Abandon	O
Somalia	LOC
,	O
Please	O
Do	O
n't	O
-	O
http://t.co/TKBBbODzPI	O
http://t.co/gg8S9Sb87u	O

RT	O
@	LOC
IWA_UK	LOC
:	O
Ever	O
wondered	O
how	O
early	O
narrow	O
boats	O
evolved	O
to	O
become	O
the	O
boats	O
we	O
see	O
on	O
#waterways	O
today	O
?	O
http://t.co/dKvlp7SdXz	O
http://t.co…	O

@	PER
lennutrajektoor	PER
Why	O
the	O
army	O
of	O
#Ukraine	LOC
kills	O
his	O
people	O
?	O

RT	O
@	PER
cross_ghetto	PER
:	O
Sarcelles	ORG
95	O
http://t.co/XRu0azqeSM	O

@projectgamer101	O
Potty	LOC
Tart	LOC
Walkways	LOC
.	O
Standout	O
.	O
Perfect	O
game	O
.	O
iTUNES	ORG
:	O
http://t.co/Bdh2unwVn7	O
Google	ORG
Play	O
:	O
http://t.co/gSTlgZuXQU	O
#JollySweets	PER

http://t.co/lI3xo2oKcP	ORG

Oxford	LOC
's	O
new	O
wastewater	O
system	O
expected	O
to	O
be	O
ready	O
in	O
September	O
http://t.co/NxYqd4pg0X	O

RT	O
@	PER
lovee_maggie	PER
:	O
If	O
it	O
makes	O
y	O
'	O
all	O
so	O
sick	O
stop	O
looking	O
@	O
it	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O

Bethany	PER
Strapless	O
Top	O
Low	O
Rise	O
Bottom	O
Bikini	O
in	O
aqua	O
Item	O
No	O
.	O
:	O
DP	O
46609	O
-	O
1	O
Price	O
:	O
$	O
30	O
.	O
99	O
(	O
Was	O
$	O
39	O
.	O
99	O
!	O
)	O
Sizes	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/TCMBlxuyAw	O

@anonymo76474365	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
id	O
love	O
to	O
be	O
that	O
toy	O
lol	O

Alas	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
yarn	O
bombing	O
component	O
of	O
the	O
@	ORG
araeslhora	ORG
campaign	O
.	O
Why	O
not	O
@	PER
CivitiMarti	PER
?	O
http://t.co/Kn5X5Kv8N5	O

RT	O
@	PER
justinbieber	PER
:	O
Good	O
times	O

“	O
@	PER
theOfficialcjay	PER
:	O
i	O
wanna	O
have	O
a	O
movie	O
night	O
�?	O
dooo	O
it	O

Fuel	O
�?	O
#filter	O
#likeforlikes	O
#likeforshoutout	O
#likeforlikealways	O
#tags	O
#likeforcomment	O
#anime	O
http://t.co/FCXhpn3UW8	O

RT	O
@ohteenposts	O
:	O
i	O
dont	O
need	O
a	O
boyfriend	O
i	O
need	O
12	O
million	O
dollars	O
and	O
a	O
donut	O

RT	O
@	PER
EXOTsouma	PER
:	O
Luhan	PER
or	O
Kai	PER
May	PER
I	O
remind	O
you	O
that	O
WE	O
ARE	O
ONE	O
!	O
http://t.co/A36LVtiITD	O

#	O
1	O
:	O
Aurora	ORG
10	O
-	O
60	O
W	O
/	O
VA	O
Dimmable	O
Low	O
Voltage	O
Electronic	O
Transformer	O
http://t.co/tYOF9riZdr	O
Aurora	ORG
10	O
-	O
60	O
W	O
/	O
VA	O
Dim	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/yyXE7U7Qbk	O

@	PER
justinbieber	PER
Happy	O
Birthday	O
:	O
)	O
Be	O
the	O
happiest	O
person	O
on	O
the	O
earth	LOC
.	O
)	O
)	O
I	O
LOVE	O
YOU	O
:	O
3	O

�?	O

Damn	O
,	O
here	O
they	O
come	O
-	O
-	O
>	O
http://t.co/6KY0XBdiJT	O

RT	O
@	PER
Ms_Temms	PER
:	O
Bless	O
the	O
Lord	O
,	O
O	O
my	O
soul	O
:	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
is	O
within	O
me	O
,	O
bless	O
his	O
holy	O
name	O
.	O
http://t.co/8W3UTVjNOc	O

My	O
mama	O
is	O
so	O
goofy	O
😂	O

@	PER
ttouchmahbutt	PER
No	O
one	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
i	O
Was	O
thinking	O
about	O
shannons	PER
ex	O
lol	O

RT	O
@	PER
FreeBeacon	PER
:	O
Showdown	O
:	O
@	PER
edhenryTV	PER
vs	O
.	O
@	PER
PressSec	PER
:	O
White	ORG
House	ORG
Wo	O
n't	O
Say	O
if	O
Border	O
is	O
Secure	O
http://t.co/PpkVEhGU8q	O
http://t.co/vLvU8Qwn4P	O

RT	O
@	ORG
TheMattEspinosa	ORG
:	O
New	O
vine	O
!	O
!	O
:)	O

RT	O
@	PER
Dory	PER
:	O
snapchat	ORG
stories	O
r	O
fun	O
bc	O
u	O
see	O
everything	O
u	O
were	O
n't	O
invited	O
to	O

Video	O
Collaboration	O
on	O
iPads	O
and	O
Android	O
Tablets	O
|	O
The	O
Vidyo	O
Blog	O
http://t.co/smAQDQsrZh	O

http://t.co/6j5J12e5QW	O

RT	O
@	PER
SoNostalgic	PER
:	O
Schoolboy	ORG
BBQ	ORG
is	O
just	O
goddamn	O
disrespectful	O
.	O

RT	O
@	PER
YellowOLLG	PER
:	O
cutest	O
thing	O
ever	O
�?	O
https://t.co/rdZjppp1d8	O

RT	O
@	PER
goodluckashley	PER
:	O
There	O
's	O
only	O
a	O
small	O
group	O
of	O
people	O
that	O
will	O
always	O
be	O
there	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
Best	O
lesson	O
I	O
've	O
learned	O
I	O
'm	O
the	O
worst	O
ways	O

So	O
much	O
heartache	O
,	O
so	O
much	O
pain	O
.	O
But	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
lessons	O
.	O

RT	O
@xDeceive	O
:	O
@xChaai	O
put	O
a	O
red	O
arrow	O
mark	O
on	O
your	O
forehead	O
and	O
go	O
as	O
ACOG	ORG

@	PER
Cattnipper	PER
Mmm	O
,	O
bit	O
too	O
piss-taking	O
,	O
might	O
turn	O
it	O
into	O
(	O
more	O
of	O
)	O
a	O
farce	O
.	O

RT	O
@	PER
Obeywesli	PER
:	O
Thot	O
earrings	O
http://t.co/jYOZsCVmXF	O

Feb	O
22	O
,	O
Sant	ORG
Andreu	ORG
Hotels	ORG
and	O
ApartHotels	ORG
http://t.co/u3z7cJ0zlR	O
via	O
@	PER
simonharris	PER

Yeah	O
works	O
boring	O
.	O
#bored	O
#tired	O

RT	O
@Za1d	O
:	O
If	O
you	O
support	O
Israel	LOC
after	O
reading	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
'm	O
sure	O
you	O
're	O
a	O
heartless	O
prick	O
.	O
#FreePalestine	LOC
http://t.co/FaRh29Llcn	O

I	O
posted	O
a	O
new	O
photo	O
to	O
Facebook	ORG
http://t.co/pTJWx9xvfi	O

Must	O
Read	O
and	O
Share	O
http://t.co/NuYddyE5MG	O

RT	O
@	PER
JoshSmith05_23	PER
:	O
I	O
'm	O
tried	O
as	O
hell	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
dick	O
not	O
.	O

@sognojoickev	O
hey	O
bella	PER
💕	O

#CitizensBank:	ORG
#manufacturing	O
leading	O
growth	O
in	O
Western	LOC
and	LOC
Central	LOC
#Massachusetts.	LOC
http://t.co/JYNtsHM8Zb	O

RT	O
@	PER
HimymCraig	PER
:	O
That	O
's	O
a	O
wrap	O
.	O
#HIMYM	O
#grateful	O

I	O
should	O
really	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O

Over	O
It	O
?	O

Boom	O
another	O
little	O
accy	O
up	O
flying	O
!	O

RT	O
@	ORG
RealSneakers_	ORG
:	O
http://t.co/OlIYutQtXz	O

Wen	O
wil	O
our	O
girls	O
return	O
?	O
If	O
our	O
govt	O
claim	O
nt	O
2	O
ve	O
d	O
manpower	O
2	O
brng	O
dem	O
back	O
,	O
atleast	O
im	O
certain	O
dey	O
have	O
d	O
money	O
2buy	O
evryone	O
of	O
dem	O
back	O

Making	O
my	O
Oscar	O
picks	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
a	O
day	O
before	O
awards	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
have	O
insights	O
for	O
a	O
full	O
predictions	O
post	O
like	O
last	O
year	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
share	O
my	O
ballot	O
later	O

OK	O
Up	O
early	O
posted	O
Racing	O
releases	O
.	O
.	O
Including	O
.	O
.	O
NASCAR	ORG
,	O
Sprint	ORG
cup	ORG
and	O
more	O
.	O
.	O
Lebanon	LOC
MO	LOC
.	O
With	O
three	O
Releases	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/Hb54OAmEFq	O

Hovel	O
has	O
been	O
upgraded	O
!	O
Can	O
you	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
?	O
Download	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
!	O
http://t.co/LCr3LZmGoS	O
#android,	O
#androidgames,	O
#gameinsight	O

“	O
@gvldsaiyan	O
:	O
how	O
little	O
dick	O
niggas	O
across	O
America	LOC
felt	O
when	O
Karlie	PER
Redd	PER
said	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
#themilitia	O
https://t.co/FyhVoZq9Eo	O
�?	O
bruh	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O

Ok	O
bye	O
yall	O
.	O
.	O
work	O
n	O
the	O
morning	O

i	O
keep	O
to	O
myself	O

Bianca	PER
Del	PER
Rio	PER
is	O
everything	O

Got	O
the	O
trap	O
house	O
jumping	O
like	O
jordan	LOC

RT	O
@goldenxvybz	O
:	O
Orange	O
is	O
the	O
new	O
black	O
till	O
I	O

@	PER
tallt33baby	PER
youre	O
a	O
savior	O

Visiting	O
my	O
4th	O
country	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
#jetsetter	O
#LovingLife	O

Love	O
is	O
always	O
there	O
for	O
you	O
💛	O
just	O
keep	O
waiting	O
💙	O

Check	O
out	O
Sasha	PER
DiGiulian	PER
Climbs	O
South	LOC
African	LOC
First	O
Ascent	O
http://t.co/guBfauNM5i	O

Hockey	O
season	O
could	O
n't	O
come	O
any	O
slower	O
.	O

@	PER
triyantinii	PER
thanks	O
teh	O

#Fitness	O
#Instructors	O
in	O
#Milwaukee.	LOC
Preview	O
our	O
summer	O
collection	O
on	O
Thursday	O
from	O
5	O
:3	O
30	O
-	O
8	O
:3	O
30	O
pm	O
.	O
Instructors	O
get	O
30	O
%	O
off	O
full	O
priced	O
items	O

We	O
're	O
playing	O
Mafia	ORG
in	O
accounting	O
🙈	O
#MockTrialMemories	O

@null	O
14	O

Cwok	O
itu	O
egois	O
-	O
_	O
-	O

Your	O
tumultuous	O
feelings	O
cross	O
over	O
into	O
public	O
domain	O
today	O
w	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
More	O
for	O
Pisces	O
http://t.co/hjJD76ani3	O

RT	O
@	ORG
namstagram	ORG
:	O
Because	O
Sunggyu	ORG
x	O
eyeliner	O
is	O
the	O
otp4	O
lyf	O
http://t.co/oJIC1B8cbo	O

RT	O
@	ORG
FollowmySteve	ORG
:	O
“	O
@	PER
divine_Opulence	PER
:	O
I	O
'm	O
never	O
drinking	O
again	O
�?	O
we	O
've	O
all	O
said	O
it	O
but	O
we	O
lie	O
to	O
ourselves	O

I	O
AM	O
SO	O
HAPPY	O
TODAY	O

SUKSES	O
!	O

#ElksChat	ORG
Last	O
day	O
of	O
Grand	ORG
Lodge	ORG
convention	O
.	O
Awards	O
being	O
given	O
to	O
winners	O
.	O
http://t.co/5HX6d2ySbQ	O

'	O
bad	O
to	O
the	O
bone	O
'	O
playing	O
on	O
@	ORG
BIKERfm	ORG
.	O
How	O
'd	O
you	O
like	O
to	O
meet	O
this	O
bad	O
boy	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
alley	O
?	O
http://t.co/1j93oA0wvm	O
http://t.co/0fKwhBdjOU	O

@	PER
NiallOfficial	PER
I	O
know	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
see	O
this	O
,	O
you	O
never	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
wanted	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
and	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
'll	O
notice	O
me	O
one	O
day	O
.	O
x20	O
,	O
248	O

http://t.co/ooEogZbhBq	O

@	PER
bronk	PER
THE	ORG
SHARKS	ORG
!	O
THE	ORG
SHARKS	ORG
!	O
You	O
just	O
made	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
dad	PER
's	O
morning	O
.	O

we	O
sub	O
tweeting	O
like	O
a	O
hoee	O
!	O
Cx	O

Ashton	PER
and	O
niallftsbrad	PER
yesterday	O
http://t.co/Jk7vIMpb3m	O

Everytime	O
somebody	O
tweets	O
"	O
read	O
my	O
bio	O
"	O
I	O
go	O
read	O
it	O
&	O
it	O
's	O
always	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
bullshit	O
.	O
.	O

RT	O
@	PER
kidrxuhl1D	PER
:	O
if	O
this	O
does	O
n't	O
make	O
you	O
smile	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
something	O
wrong	O
with	O
you	O
https://t.co/qSJTHNk9u8	O

@	PER
_DANNiBanani	PER
Thank	O
you	O
love	O
😘	O

It	O
's	O
GAMEDAY	O
on	O
The	LOC
Hill	LOC
!	O
Girls	ORG
LAX	ORG
vs	O
Centennial	ORG
.	O
1st	O
rd	O
of	O
State	O
Playoffs	O
@	O
HOME	LOC
!	O
Starts	O
@	O
7	O
pm	O
.	O
Need	O
to	O
pack	O
the	O
house	O
for	O
our	O
girls	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

@	PER
glauer11	PER
What	O
is	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
life	O
?	O

Played	O
in	O
a	O
pool	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
new	O
meaning	O
to	O
'	O
taking	O
a	O
dive	O
'	O
#FakeWorldCupFacts	O
@midnight	O

RT	O
@	PER
LiamHaylett	PER
:	O
"	O
Tweet	O
not	O
sent	O
,	O
saved	O
to	O
drafts	O
"	O
http://t.co/gknrRiYGrJ	O

RT	O
@	PER
BoothWilliam	PER
:	O
Makeshift	O
TV	O
studio	O
at	O
Shifa	LOC
hospital	LOC
in	O
gaza	LOC
.	O
waiting	O
for	O
Islamic	O
Jihad	O
politico	O
Khalid	PER
al	PER
Batish	PER
to	O
finish	O
his	O
spin	O
htt	O
…	O

Take	O
a	O
bow	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
pretty	O
<	O
3	O

Live	O
daringly	O
,	O
boldly	O
,	O
fearlessly	O
.	O
Taste	O
the	O
relish	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
competition	O
in	O
having	O
put	O
forth	O
the	O
best	O
within	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
Henry	PER
J	PER
.	PER
Kaiser	PER

@	PER
mitchgrassi	PER
maybe	O
you	O
should	O
eat	O
more	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
?	O
A	O
little	O
bit	O
more	O
padding	O
?	O

RT	O
@	ORG
DeadlineDayLive	ORG
:	O
AS	ORG
Monaco	ORG
and	O
Real	ORG
Madrid	ORG
are	O
very	O
close	O
to	O
agreeing	O
the	O
transfer	O
of	O
James	PER
Rodríguez	PER
.	O
(	O
Source	O
:	O
AS	ORG
)	O

J	O
'	O
AI	O
MES	O
6	O
.	O
2	O
K	O
FKFLDLKDHJLD	O

How	O
's	O
you	O
Hump	O
day	O
goin	O
?	O
@	PER
AndreaOnAirMtl	PER
http://t.co/X809DYgK8N	O

Persamaan	O
cewe	O
dan	PER
cowo	O
-	O
>	O
We	O
are	O
not	O
so	O
different	O
afterall	O
http://t.co/JUPTeReFon	O
via	O
@9GAG	O

Loving	O
The	O
Checkout	O
on	O
ABC	ORG
iView	ORG
.	O
http://t.co/YZbPZXa2IV	O
http://t.co/wYKFLqNzip	O

At	O
10	O
#UNSC	ORG
will	O
discuss	O
the	O
situation	O
in	O
#Libya.	LOC
Foreign	PER
Minister	PER
Abdelaziz	PER
and	O
@	ORG
UNSMILibya	ORG
Head	PER
Mitri	PER
will	O
address	O
the	O
Council	ORG

helping	O
other	O
people	O
makes	O
me	O
happy	O
.	O
I	O
definitely	O
need	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
therapist	O

@	ORG
KingCDF	ORG
who	O
is	O
n't	O
making	O
a	O
living	O
?	O
Clown	O
.	O
And	O
on	O
that	O
spare	O
time	O
,	O
go	O
lose	O
.	O

RT	O
@	PER
justinbieber	PER
:	O
I	O
hope	O
chuck	PER
norris	PER
does	O
n't	O
try	O
to	O
shut	O
this	O
party	O
down	O

CLaw	O
exam	O
at	O
7	O
:3	O
30	O
-	O
8	O
:3	O
30	O
pm	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
Kill	O
.	O
-	O
_	O
-	O

@	PER
t_wandy_	PER
send	O
a	O
dm	O
.	O
Send	O
a	O
dm	O
send	O
a	O
dm	O

RT	O
@	PER
davelackie	PER
:	O
I	O
'm	O
giving	O
away	O
this	O
Dior	ORG
Addict	O
Fluid	O
Stick	O
Wardrobe	O
!	O
Incredible	O
product	O
!	O
To	O
enter	O
,	O
follow	O
…	O
http://t.co/rMGZomShd2	O

@	PER
viebts	PER
Hooh	O
:)	O

@	PER
YewrXdaD	PER
since	O
its	O
a	O
mothersday	O
contest	O
pic	O
has	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
u	O
n	O
ur	O
mother	O
:)	O

Oeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee	O

@	PER
KamiObare	PER
he	O
's	O
watching	O
you	O
too	O

:	O
Al-	ORG
Qaeda	ORG
:	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
's	O
Most	O
Notorious	O
Terrorist	O
Organization	O
:	O
Al-	ORG
Qaeda	ORG
:	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/2dywzLtYjS	O

RT	O
@	PER
RyanMiller3039	PER
:	O
Thank	O
you	O
to	O
everyone	O
in	O
WNY	LOC
.	O
For	O
the	O
last	O
12	O
years	O
you	O
have	O
made	O
Buffalo	LOC
and	O
Rochester	LOC
a	O
great	O
place	O
to	O
live	O
and	O
play	O
.	O

RT	O
@	PER
zaynmalik	PER
:	O
:)	O
party	O
!	O
!	O
Woo	O
thankyou	O
to	O
everyone	O
that	O
's	O
ever	O
been	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
1	ORG
D	ORG
:)	O
we	O
owe	O
this	O
night	O
to	O
you	O
!	O
!	O
Xx	O

I	O
liked	O
a	O
@YouTube	O
video	O
http://t.co/oMHYhHvO6H	O
Plants	O
vs	O
Zombies	O
Music	O
Video	O

I	O
really	O
want	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
and	O
tell	O
you	O

BACK	ORG
DROP	ORG
BOMB	ORG
Releases	O
Preview	O
Tracks	O
from	O
Tribute	O
Album	O
:	O
BACK	ORG
DROP	ORG
BOMB	ORG
reveals	O
the	O
cover	O
art	O
and	O
previews	O
f	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/mzzpM6Bp1r	O

this	O
Persian	O
shawty	O
was	O
undressing	O
me	O
with	O
her	O
eyes	O
,	O
whilst	O
with	O
her	O
man	O
😈	O
�?	O

my	O
twitter	ORG
follows	O
and	O
unfollows	O
people	O
on	O
my	O
account	O
its	O
annoying	O

:(	O
http://t.co/RTqdJs0SqO	O

@	PER
bringash1026	PER
@	PER
KevBurbano	PER
@	PER
nickoo19	PER
Yea	O
count	O
Kevin	PER
out	O
of	O
competition	O
,	O
even	O
tho	O
that	O
nigga	O
always	O
knows	O
the	O
future	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

http://t.co/Ys3ud0T1pE	O

It	O
's	O
scary	O
to	O
progress	O
ahead	O
so	O
fast	O
that	O
you	O
must	O
scramble	O
yo	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
More	O
for	O
Pisces	PER
http://t.co/aqQoTxJDLA	O

Bom	PER
Dia	PER
:(	O
:	O

“	O
@manditoosnipes1	O
:	O
I	O
miss	O
Sergio	PER
man	O
,	O
remember	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
came	O
over	O
still	O
,	O
big	O
ass	O
in	O
my	O
moms	O
Fj	ORG
cruiser	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
"	O
back	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
lil	O
Savage	O

RT	O
@	PER
Peedypa_	PER
:	O
I	O
just	O
want	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
by	O
my	O
side	O
thick	O
through	O
thin	O
.	O

Shout	O
out	O
to	O
our	O
beautiful	O
birthday	O
girl	O
@	PER
Lexinicole202	PER
hope	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
day	O
and	O
will	O
see	O
you	O
in	O
a	O
couple	O
days	O
!	O
🎉	O
🎈	O
�?	O
🎂	O

@	PER
TheMafiaAntonio	PER
@	PER
TheSaintVanity	PER
We	O
have	O
no	O
established	O
relationship	O
sweetie	O
.	O
Until	O
your	O
breaking	O
with	O
that	O
hussy	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
nobody	O
's	O
.	O
.	O

RT	O
@	PER
LittleMix	PER
:	O
I	O
've	O
been	O
deceived	O
!	O
!	O
It	O
looked	O
sunny	O
outside	O
this	O
morning	O
😔	O
#noparker	PER
xxjadexx	PER

RT	O
@	ORG
MesaRiverview	ORG
:	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
want	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
will	O
laugh	O
-	O
>	O
MT	O
@	ORG
Cinemark	ORG
:	O
In	O
case	O
you	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
Watch	O
the	O
Dumb	O
and	O
Dumber	O
To	O
trailer	O
:	O
http	O
…	O

RT	O
@	ORG
TBVines	ORG
:	O
This	O
man	O
has	O
balls	O
http://t.co/OGzvcnlctG	O

RT	O
@	PER
Alex_Godinez_	PER
:	O
Finally	O
its	O
March	O
😌	O
🌻	O
☀	O
�?	O

@	PER
mynameiscal	PER
@	PER
jenlv	PER
her	O
linkedin	ORG
must	O
be	O
getting	O
hella	O
hits	O
though	O

RT	O
@	PER
drewmart2	PER
:	O
Probally	O
the	O
best	O
so	O
far	O
https://t.co/fHlfL2GENU	O

@	PER
SadLyle	PER
@	PER
KeysFefe	PER
@	PER
Trap_nasty75	PER
@	PER
trphies	PER
why	O
would	O
someone	O
from	O
Eastridge	LOC
do	O
that	O
?	O

2012	O

Constitutional	ORG
Court	ORG
ousts	O
Thai	LOC
prime	O
minister	O
after	O
finding	O
her	O
guilty	O
in	O
abuse	O
of	O
power	O
case	O
.	O
http://t.co/9Pj6JYvzUR	O

@	PER
SavingMyBrosAss	PER
idk	O
why	O
you	O
did	O
n't	O
come	O
over	O
like	O
you	O
said	O
you	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
I	O
was	O
having	O
people	O
haha	O

Please	O
cure	O
my	O
hangover	O
?	O
http://t.co/h2xmFEVWXk	O

RT	O
@	PER
JasonKuznicki	PER
:	O
This	O
One	O
Weird	O
Trick	O
"	O
caused	O
a	O
steep	O
decline	O
in	O
both	O
forcible	O
rape	O
offenses	O
and	O
the	O
incidence	O
of	O
gonorrhea	O
.	O
"	O
http://t.co…	O

7	O
/	O
5	O
looking	O
for	O
long	O
AUDSGD	O
once	O
it	O
settles	O
after	O
poor	O
retail	O
sales	O
.	O
And	O
long	O
GBPCHF	O
is	O
setting	O
.	O
Waiting	O
for	O
BOE	ORG
though	O

matthew	PER
grey	PER
gubler	PER
is	O
so	O
fucking	O
hot	O
i	O
cant	O
believe	O

#big	O
boobs	O
the	O
#WhoreWednesday	O
#nsfw	O
#adult	O
#porn	O
#Hardcore	O
huge	O
boobs	O
galleries	O
http://t.co/NAo91YTo9p	O

Enjoy	O
your	O
favorite	O
liqueurs	O
MUCH	O
MORE	O
with	O
the	O
Luxury	O
Crystal	O
Liqueur	O
Glass	O
Monaco	LOC
http://t.co/FrTrMmlLPg	O
http://t.co/QmNWYxocFi	O

RT	O
@	PER
tity2juz	PER
:	O
Any	O
Terio	PER
slander	O
is	O
an	O
automatic	O
10	O
RT	O
's	O
y	O
'	O
all	O
so	O
unoriginal	O
.	O

@	PER
Michael5SOS	PER
you	O
make	O
me	O
happy	O

http://t.co/sm2fn6sdJo	O

If	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
in	O
planning	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
.	O
.	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
in	O
the	O
future	O
.	O

If	O
you	O
have	O
ASAP	O
anything	O
in	O
your	O
name	O
I	O
'm	O
just	O
gonna	O
assume	O
you	O
're	O
a	O
faggot	O
.	O

RT	O
@	PER
LILBTHEBASEDGOD	PER
:	O
LOVE	O
YOU	O
AND	O
YOUR	O
FAMILY	O
THANK	O
YOU	O
FOR	O
WAKING	O
UP	O
!	O
!	O
THIS	O
IS	O
FROM	O
LIL	PER
B	PER
!	O
-	O
Lil	PER
B	PER

That	O
bitch	O
made	O
me	O
choke	O
her	O
ass	O
#shitwyattsays	PER

@	PER
CalandCo	PER
I	O
'm	O
a	O
nigerian	LOC
prince	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
play	O
alicia	PER
keys	PER
(	O
as	O
i	O
am	O
)	O
i	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
$	O
1	O
.	O
m	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
.	O
all	O
hail	O
the	O
powerful	O
NA	ORG
.	O

@ALBudEBoyEnt	O
@Kokaneofficial	O
@	ORG
Soulcentralmag	ORG
@DjKingAssassin	O
@AfroNaj	O
@ACLDaBoss	O
@pence	O
@	PER
PJhewett	PER

http://t.co/4S1cgmbkAg	O

ISAAC	ORG
NEWTON	ORG
ACADEMY	ORG
:	O
Head	O
of	O
Maths	O
http://t.co/3a0CTFBFuy	O
#testhashtag	O

@	PER
sethscaglia	PER
@	PER
tuttlesydney	PER
@	ORG
PBOWMAFIA	ORG
No	O
,	O
haha	O
was	O
it	O
suppose	O
too	O
?	O

Test	O

RT	O
@Fact	O
:	O
6	O
of	O
the	O
Most	O
Heavily	O
Guarded	O
Locations	O
on	O
the	O
Planet	O
!	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/wGYI2GXaR9	O

Without	O
God	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
nothing	O
.	O

NINI	PER
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
http://t.co/I6Mj8X2khv	O

@	PER
EricaSpeaksss	PER
Yea	O
Dat	O
But	O
Still	O
It	O
Is	O

My	O
new	O
partner	O
-	O
_	O
-	O

@	PER
JuggManMike	PER
that	O
's	O
not	O
even	O
fair	O
I	O
'm	O
on	O
episode	O
11	O

RT	O
@	PER
AlfredoFlores	PER
:	O
Happy	O
Birthday	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
.	O
Ai	O
n't	O
so	O
little	O
anymore	O
!	O
What	O
a	O
journey	O
it	O
's	O
been	O
.	O
Here	O
's	O
to	O
many	O
more	O
…	O
http://t.co/0QhEfy…	O

Had	O
a	O
great	O
night	O
with	O
my	O
girl	O
@	PER
oliviad5050	PER
(	O
:	O

@	PER
beasoje	PER
everybody	O
say	O
yes	O

When	O
you	O
have	O
something	O
that	O
everyone	O
else	O
wants	O
😜	O
�?	O
😒	O

Photo	O
:	O
http://t.co/v8sYpPCwl9	O

RT	O
@	PER
StefKoJoHoe	PER
:	O
Such	O
a	O
great	O
night	O
:)	O

RT	O
@	PER
Real_Liam_Payne	PER
:	O
Well	O
there	O
's	O
not	O
gunna	O
b	O
much	O
sleeping	O
tonight	O
👂	O
👈	O
lol	O

#	O
1	O
:	O
Whiskey	O
Stones	O
-	O
9	O
Soapstone	O
Chilling	O
Cubes	O
in	O
a	O
Magnetic	O
Designer	O
Box	O
with	O
Black	O
Velvet	O
Bag	O
,	O
an	O
Awesome	O
Gift	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/spVW57WvWD	O

RT	O
@	PER
DJTayJames	PER
:	O
With	O
some	O
good	O
friends	O
@	PER
lolliecakez	PER
@	PER
_jortiz	PER
http://t.co/I6AkteQJKy	O
#selfie	O
http://t.co/WRS8hBQS8t	O

@love_an_artist	O
:	O
@	PER
CharlesBivona	PER
@	PER
ggreenwald	PER
"	O
another	O
8	O
.	O
.	O
yrs	O
under	O
a	O
Clinton	PER
.	O
.	O
.	O
better	O
than	O
8	O
more	O
Bush	PER
yrs	O
"	O
Actually	O
they	O
'd	O
be	O
about	O
the	O
same	O

Defqon	O
1	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

RT	O
@	PER
CaseyVeggies	PER
:	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
no	O
way	O
we	O
can	O
lose	O
�?	O

@	PER
jasmine_hutton	PER
I	O
made	O
waffles	O
😂	O

Did	O
you	O
ever	O
love	O
me	O
like	O
I	O
ever	O
love	O
you	O
?	O
It	O
's	O
my	O
mistake	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
do	O
right	O
nobody	O
remember	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
'm	O
wrong	O
they	O
remember	O
it	O
frv	O

6	O
days	O
still	O
my	O
town	O
hall	O
upgrades	O
to	O
level	O
7	O
?	O
That	O
's	O
crazy	O
.	O

Success	O
for	O
Holgate	ORG
’	O
s	O
film	O
studies	O
students	O
in	O
Young	ORG
Creative	ORG
Awards	ORG
:	O
Students	O
from	O
Holgate	ORG
Academy	ORG
attended	O
t	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/A7ircD6kvj	O

My	O
dogs	O
such	O
a	O
meat	O
head	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
She	O
broke	O
her	O
collar	O
by	O
running	O
straight	O
off	O
her	O
dog	O
run	O
.	O
.	O
Cool	O
.	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
the	O
hulk	O

Grace	O
,	O
faith	O
,	O
wisdom	O
,	O
strength	O
,	O
&	O
patience	O
.	O

@	PER
HerTinyElephant	PER
thank	O
you	O
and	O
thank	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
for	O
adding	O
me	O
to	O
your	O
list	O
:)	O
<	O
3	O

RT	O
@	PER
drinkingsmokin	PER
:	O
You	O
can	O
smoke	O
weed	O
and	O
still	O
be	O
successful	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
all	O
on	O
you	O
.	O

Boehner	PER
wasting	O
ink	O
filing	O
for	O
re-election	O
=	O
=	O
>	O
http://t.co/GelmDjgpWQ	O
We	O
#Benghazi	LOC
remember	O
U	O
on	O
HRes	O
36	O
#PJNET	O
#JusticeForBenghazi4	LOC

RT	O
@	PER
Sunayyaaa	PER
:	O
Oomf	O
be	O
talking	O
about	O
she	O
need	O
a	O
perm	O
every	O
week	O
lmao	O

But	O
i	O
dont	O
want	O
to	O
be	O
like	O
that	O
.	O
Lebih	O
rela	O
cmtok	O
dr	O
dpt	O
pgganti	O
yg	O
belom	O
tntu	O
baik	O
and	O
dpt	O
trimak	O
seadanya	LOC
.	O

@	PER
FellyciousEVT	PER
thx	O
:)	O

I	O
think	O
I	O
'm	O
the	O
only	O
one	O
who	O
gets	O
mad	O
when	O
I	O
forget	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
period	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
a	O
tweet	O
.	O

Bueh	O

Have	O
n't	O
felt	O
this	O
shit	O
in	O
a	O
long	O
time	O

RT	O
@	PER
i_m_justinbiebe	PER
:	O
Oh	O
!	O
Canada	LOC
!	O
No	O
,	O
really	O
.	O
Oh	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Canada	LOC
.	O
These	O
photos	O
could	O
only	O
be	O
from	O
Canada	LOC
!	O
http://t.co/GRYqSOC4wh	O

Smh	O
practice	O
at	O
4	O
really	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
game	O

RT	O
@	PER
DavidRoads	PER
:	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
find	O
peace	O
by	O
avoiding	O
life	O
.	O

RT	O
@	PER
SayDatAgain	PER
:	O
Haha	O
!	O
RT	O
@	ORG
TheCosby	ORG
:	O
Black	O
Captain	O
America	LOC
not	O
recognized	O
in	O
Michigan	LOC
because	O
of	O
affirmative	O
action	O
accusations	O

Rolling	O
Laker	ORG
Blunts	O
!	O
S	O
/	O
o	O
to	O
Kobe	PER
!	O

RT	O
@	PER
AniqahC	PER
:	O
#introvertpickuplines	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
beautiful	O
I	O
'd	O
let	O
you	O
into	O
my	O
Personal	O
Space	O
bubble	O
(	O
only	O
for	O
a	O
limited	O
amount	O
of	O
time	O
or	O
I	O
g	O
…	O

RT	O
@	PER
wesrucker247	PER
:	O
Whatever	O
Ant	PER
Barton	PER
ate	O
for	O
breakfast	O
,	O
#Vols	ORG
should	O
keep	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
menu	O
.	O

😲	O
The	O
1st	O
thing	O
I	O
see	O
on	O
Twitter	ORG
today	O
RT	O
@	PER
Adventuree_Time	PER
:	O
Welp	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
unsee	O
this	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
'm	O
making	O
y	O
'	O
all	O
see	O
it	O
too	O
.	O
http://t.co/K9b4WtABde	O

I	O
am	O
Alpha	O
and	O
Omega	O
,	O
the	O
beginning	O
and	O
the	O
ending	O
,	O
saith	O
the	O
Lord	PER
,	O
which	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
is	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
t	O
…	O
http://t.co/LIL7UUWg76	O

.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

@	PER
xyoofficial	PER
Sure	O
!	O
Anything	O
for	O
you	O
!	O

The	O
definition	O
of	O
UNTIL	O
-	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
.	O
When	O
it	O
comes	O
to	O
health	O
and	O
fitness	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
end	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
something	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/Bi9UpQjXZQ	O

“	O
@	PER
BadAdviceDog	PER
:	O
dont	O
send	O
nudes	O
…	O
send	O
xrays	O
its	O
whats	O
inside	O
that	O
counts	O
�?	O
@	PER
sarachom	PER

@	PER
h_poulter	PER
Just	O
like	O
you	O
,	O
your	O
team	O
never	O
turned	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Brit	LOC
.	O
.	O
.	O
again	O
!	O
1	O
-	O
0	O
to	O
the	O
Rugby	O
Team	O
!	O
#SwingLow	O
#OneRyanShawcross	PER
#ByeByeTitle	O
:-D	O

I	O
'm	O
scared	O
a	O
college	O
is	O
gonna	O
reject	O
me	O
cause	O
I	O
did	O
n't	O
share	O
that	O
photo	O
of	O
Jesus	PER
on	O
the	O
cross	O
on	O
facebook	O
.	O

RT	O
@	ORG
Deadspin	ORG
:	O
VIDEO	O
:	O
If	O
you	O
need	O
inspiration	O
for	O
today	O
or	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
your	O
life	O
,	O
watch	O
Stuart	PER
Scott	PER
's	O
moving	O
ESPY	ORG
speech	O
:	O
http://t.co/n…	O

@	PER
BIG_Jason77	PER
ahhh	O
true	O
!	O
!	O

Now	O
Playing	O
:	O
Happy	O
by	O
Pharrell	PER
Williams	PER
on	O
Urban	ORG
Radio	ORG
-	O
Adult	O
Hits	O
http://t.co/XUXX0uJ1z2	O

RT	O
@	PER
elzamega	PER
:	O
nothing	O
but	O
is	O
something	O
!	O

Come	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
bearday	O
tomorrow	O
and	O
i	O
have	O
a	O
date	O
with	O
the	O
wrong	O
bestfriend	O
:))	O

RT	O
@	PER
DaveProps	PER
:	O
Look	O
who	O
's	O
bar	O
tending	O
!	O
#Himym	O
#PamFryman	PER
http://t.co/nY6twCdlwk	O

I	O
ca	O
n't	O
do	O
this	O
8	O
o'clock	O
class	O
😤	O
🙅	O

http://t.co/cuGiqeYrxl	O
#	O
3	O
:	O
3	ORG
M	ORG
Utility	O
Duct	O
Tape	O
2929	O
Silver	O
,	O
1	O
-	O
22	O
/	O
25	O
in	O
x	O
50	O
yd	O
5	O
.	O
8	O
mils	O
(	O
Pack	O
of	O
1	O
)	O
3	ORG
M	ORG
Utilit	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/eNHGzZe8Mc	O

@	PER
KWanhatalo	PER
made	O
fun	O
of	O
my	O
username	O
so	O
i	O
changed	O
it	O

http://t.co/dFzCytXbDL	O

A	O
second	O
reason	O
for	O
this	O
blog	O
is	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
these	O
#Bible	O
#prophecies	O
are	O
being	O
fulfilled	O
in	O
our	O
current	O
times	O
.	O
http://t.co/1s7CHEKpN2	O

http://t.co/ftpiBZrcR4	O
16407967716	O

March	O
is	O
my	O
favorite	O
Month	O

Chase	O

I	O
did	O
n't	O
notice	O
the	O
time	O

@	PER
MaxiBlumhagen	PER
pasame	O
a	O
buscar	O
hajajajajajajjaja	O

RT	O
@	PER
ashleykelleher7	PER
:	O
I	O
Do	O
Not	O
Feel	O
Good	O

AYE	O

RT	O
@	PER
IbnSaeed2	PER
:	O
#ModelTownTragedy	O
Women	O
affected	O
by	O
the	O
police	O
shelling	O
.	O
http://t.co/GnTb1DzFFO	O

HELP	O
WANTED	O
!	O
!	O
Hi	O
Everyone	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
looking	O
for	O
people	O
who	O
want	O
to	O
be	O
distributors	O
for	O
Skinny	ORG
Fiber	ORG
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/8AtueXDvrQ	O

Huge	O
tune	O
from	O
the	O
boys	O
Standard	ORG
Procedure	ORG
Dubstep	ORG
&	O
p0	ORG
gman	ORG
Dubstep	ORG
!	O
!	O
!	O
http://t.co/MjA5P7CBqq	O

Tip	O
toeing	O
in	O
my	O
jawdins	O
lol	O

RT	O
@BestTextMsgs	O
:	O
I	O
'm	O
really	O
hoping	O
something	O
good	O
happens	O
between	O
us	O
.	O

http://t.co/2khQjl1ms4	ORG

@RP_RonW	O
check	O
you	O
owl	O
=)	O
)	O
)	O
-	O
tc	O

@	PER
MikeAndMike	PER
Hey	O
greeny	O
if	O
you	O
didnt	O
see	O
the	O
fight	O
and	O
only	O
read	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Bubba	PER
saw	O
the	O
fight	O
,	O
hey	O
greeny	O
Shut	O
Up	O
your	O
an	O
idiot	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

@	PER
Harry_Styles	PER
come	O
to	O
australia	LOC

@bravenewmalden	O
I	O
thought	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
default	O
setting	O
?	O

RT	O
@DumbLawz	O
:	O
Ugly	O
women	O
must	O
call	O
out	O
“	O
Hideous	O
Hag	O
Coming	O
�?	O
before	O
entering	O
a	O
building	O
where	O
men	O
may	O
be	O
.	O
(	O
Delaware	LOC
)	O

RT	O
@	PER
Ashton5SOS	PER
:	O
London	LOC
is	O
gorgeous	O
this	O
afternoon	O
http://t.co/xxBkz6xObM	O

RT	O
@FamousBirthdays	O
:	O
Wishing	O
a	O
Happy	O
20th	O
Birthday	O
to	O
Justin	PER
Bieber	PER
@	PER
JustinBieber	PER
http://t.co/s2dOvFpGvH	O

@	PER
PadmajaJoshi	PER
@	PER
DhanushKool	PER
India	LOC
is	O
helpless	O
,	O
can	O
not	O
protect	O
dignity	O
of	O
its	O
women	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
not	O
that	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
even	O
tried	O
yet	O
!	O

Hay	O

Kkkkk	O

@	PER
_eboniwalker	PER
well	O
extreme	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
what	O
u	O
have	O
in	O
mind	O
,	O
but	O
yes	O
extreme	O
as	O
in	O
rapid	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'm	O
manic	O
dnt	O
sleep	O
for	O
6	O
-	O
7	O
days	O
then	O
crash	O
hard	O

Three	O
Ways	O
To	O
Save	O
at	O
Hancock	LOC
Fabrics	LOC
This	O
Week	O
via	O
Couponing	O
4	O
You	O
-	O
Three	O
HOT	O
new	O
ways	O
to	O
save	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/q9HpiXdk0t	O

"	O
orgy	O
of	O
evidence	O
"	O
okay	O
will	O

@	PER
ashvasant	PER
Is	O
it	O
true	O
that	O
jindal	PER
gave	O
him	O
30	O
cr	O
for	O
Varanasi	LOC
campaign	O
?	O

@	PER
katodm	PER
@	PER
BlackVines_	PER
thirst	O
level	O
100	O

The	O
way	O
she	O
still	O
carried	O
on	O
😩	O
😂	O
https://t.co/IHsGBN6cSO	O

RT	O
@	PER
chadcollins27	PER
:	O
Omg	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
Holy	O
fug	O
!	O
!	O

RT	O
@	PER
DachaQueen	PER
:	O
SMA	O
?	O
Full	O
of	O
shit	O
